<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sunscreen &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<atom:link href="http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/danh-muc-san-pham/skincare/sunscreen/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:22:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>vi</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/favicon.png</url>
	<title>Sunscreen &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ultimate Sun Protection Spray Broad Spectrum SPF 50+ For Face/Body</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/ultimate-sun-protection-spray-broad-spectrum-spf-50-for-face-body/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/ultimate-sun-protection-spray-broad-spectrum-spf-50-for-face-body/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:19:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=469</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Rose Apple Leaf Extract: Counteracts oxidation, the process which accelerates skin aging, and helps prevent DNA damage caused by UV rays.
-Super-Veil 360: Provides extreme skin protection; allows sunscreen to fit perfectly on the uneven surface of the skin providing high protection from UV rays at all angles.
-Profense CEL: Supports natural protection of cells and DNA from UV damage by supporting enzyme activity which is the cause of future uneven skin tone and wrinkles.
-Xylitol: Helps keep skin soft and healthy-looking.
-Avobenzone 3%, Homosalate 15%, Octisalate 5%, Octocrylene 2.5%, Oxybenzone 5%: Provide sun protection properties.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is:</b><br />
A convenient spray sunscreen that allows quick, easy application over large areas of skin, especially hard-to-reach areas.</p>
<p><b>What it is formulated to do:</b><br />
This sunscreen spray provides broad spectrum protection, protecting skin against powerful UV rays, while skin care ingredients maintain skin’s beauty. With its light texture, it feels comfortable with no stickiness or greasy residue. Easy to use, it is water resistant and great for use on face, body, and hair for complete coverage.</p>
<p><b>What else you need to know:</b><br />
This product is water-, sweat-, and oil-resistant.</p>
<p><b>Research results:</b><br />
Tested by 125 women:<br />
&#8211; 95% say the formulation spreads lightly on the skin<br />
&#8211; 95% said they want to continue using this product</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/ultimate-sun-protection-spray-broad-spectrum-spf-50-for-face-body/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Daily UV Defense Invisible Broad Spectrum SPF 36 Sunscreen</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/daily-uv-defense-invisible-broad-spectrum-spf-36-sunscreen/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/daily-uv-defense-invisible-broad-spectrum-spf-36-sunscreen/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=467</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Avobenzone 2.5%, Homosalate 7%, and Octisalate 4.3%

Water / Aqua / Eau, Butylene Glycol, Cyclopentasiloxane, Butyloctyl Salicylate, Ethylhexyl Methoxycrylene, Arachidyl Alcohol, Behenyl Alcohol, Glyceryl Stearate, Peg-100 Stearate, 1,2-Hexanediol, Polymethylsilsesquioxane, Cetyl Alcohol, Arachidyl Glucoside, Phenoxyethanol, Propanediol, Polyacrylate Crosspolymer-6, Octyldodecanol, Fragrance / Parfum, Xanthan Gum, Centella Asiatica Extract, Portulaca Oleracea Extract, Echium Plantagineum Seed Oil, T-Butyl Alcohol, Camellia Sinensis Leaf Extract, Ethylhexylglycerin, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Oil Unsaponifiables, Cardiospermum Halicacabum Flower/Leaf/Vine Extract, Tocopherol, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Oil, Glycerin, Hamamelis Virginiana (Witch Hazel) Leaf Extract, Citrus Unshiu Peel Extract, Opuntia Coccinellifera Fruit Extract, Orchid Extract, Camellia Japonica Leaf Extract, Citric Acid, Sodium Benzoate, Potassium Sorbate.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>What it is: </strong>A lightweight, daily Broad Spectrum SPF 36 sunscreen delivering invisible sun protection while hydrating and soothing skin &#8211; no white-cast, just glow!</p>
<p><strong>Skin Type: </strong>Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><strong>Skincare Concerns: </strong>Dryness</p>
<p><strong>Formulation: </strong>Lightweight Cream</p>
<p><strong>Highlighted Ingredients:</strong></p>
<p>&#8211; Green Tea: Nurtures skin with soothing hydration.</p>
<p>&#8211; Cica: Soothes skin and reduces visible signs of irritation.</p>
<p>&#8211; Sunflower Seed Oil: Delivers lightweight moisture to skin.</p>
<p><strong>Ingredient Callouts:</strong> Free of sulfates SLS and SLES, parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, triclosan, and triclocarban, and contains less than one percent of synthetic fragrances.</p>
<p><strong>What Else You Need to Know: </strong>This sunscreen is infused with a blend of green tea, cica, and sunflower seed oil for three-in-one benefits; it hydrates, soothes, and protects. The lightweight formula delivers undetectable sun protection with SPF 36 while giving skin giving a fresh-looking glow.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/daily-uv-defense-invisible-broad-spectrum-spf-36-sunscreen/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
