<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Blemish &amp; Acne Treatments &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<atom:link href="http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/tu-khoa-san-pham/blemish-acne-treatments/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:24:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>vi</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/favicon.png</url>
	<title>Blemish &amp; Acne Treatments &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Cicapair ™ Tiger Grass Camo Drops Color Corrector SPF 35</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/cicapair-tiger-grass-camo-drops-color-corrector-spf-35/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/cicapair-tiger-grass-camo-drops-color-corrector-spf-35/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=458</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Mineral Sunscreen (Zinc Oxide and Titanium Dioxide): Reflects UVA/UVB rays, protecting skin from sun damage.

Cyclopentasiloxane, <i>Centella asiatica</i> Extract, Isononyl Isononanoate, Butylene Glycol, Titanium Dioxide, Zinc Oxide, Glycerin, Niacinamide, Polymethylsilsesquioxane, Methyl Methacrylate Crosspolymer, Water, Sodium Chloride, Disteardimonium Hectorite, Iron Oxides (CI 77492), Aluminum Hydroxide, Triethoxycaprylylsilane, Acrylates/Dimethicone Copolymer, Chromium Oxide Greens, Beeswax, Disodium EDTA, Asiaticoside, Hydrogenated Lecithin, Lavandula Angustifolia (Lavender) Oil, Asiatic Acid, Rosmarinus Officinalis (Rosemary) Leaf Oil, <i>Centella asiatica</i> Leaf Water, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Oil, Houttuynia Cordata Extract, Alcohol, Caprylic/Capric Triglyceride, Phenoxyethanol, Anthemis Nobilis Flower Oil, Lecithin, Arnica Montana Flower Extract, Aniba Rosaeodora (Rosewood) Wood Oil, Ethylhexylglycerin, Madecassoside, Methyl Trimethicone, Butyloctyl Salicylate, Pentaerythrityl Tetraisostearate, Diphenysiloxy Phenyl Trimethicone, Dipropylene Glycol, Isododecane, Lauryl PEG-10 Tris (Trimethysiloxy) Silylethyl Dimethicone, Magnesium Sulfate, Polyglyceryl-4 Isostearate, Dipentaerythrityl Hexahydroxystearate / Hexastearate / Hexarosinate, 1,2-Hexanediol, Iron Oxides (CI 77491), Caprylyl Glycol, Synthetic Fluorphlogopite, Glyceryl Caprylate, Zein, Silica Dimethyl Silylate, Adenosine, Zea Mays (Corn) Starch, Citrus Paradisi (Grapefruit) Peel Oil, Dipotassium Phosphate, Calcium Stearate, Gossypium Herbaceum (Cotton) Seed Oil, Panthenol, Tocopherol, Anastatica Hierochuntica Extract, Pentylene Glycol, Magnesium Aspartate, Zinc Gluconate, Brassica Campestris (Rapeseed) Sterols, Leuconostoc / Radish Root Ferment Filtrate, Sucrose Laurate, Polyglyceryl-2 Caprate, Fragaria Vesca (Strawberry) Fruit Extract, Lysolecithin, Ceramide NP, Copper Gluconate, Sodium Ascorbyl Phosphate, Madecassic Acid.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A lightweight green-to-beige color corrector with a serum-like texture, dewy finish, and SPF to rapidly neutralize the look of redness and visibly ignite skin’s glow.</p>
<p><b>Skin Type:</b> Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><b>Skincare Concerns:</b> Redness and Dullness</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Mineral Sunscreen (Zinc Oxide and Titanium Dioxide): Reflects UVA/UVB rays, protecting skin from sun damage.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> For centuries, tigers in the Asian wetlands have rolled around in <i>Centella asiatica</i> (aka tiger grass or cica) to help heal their wounds. Taking inspiration from the tigers, this K-beauty favorite utilizes visibly reparative tiger grass to soothe, calm, and moisturize skin.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/cicapair-tiger-grass-camo-drops-color-corrector-spf-35/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
