<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Paula&#8217;s Choice &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<atom:link href="http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/danh-muc-san-pham/brands/paulas-choice/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 13:10:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>vi</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/favicon.png</url>
	<title>Paula&#8217;s Choice &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>C15 Vitamin C Super Booster</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/c15-vitamin-c-super-booster/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/c15-vitamin-c-super-booster/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 13:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=539</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Vitamin C (L-Ascorbic Acid) 15%: Visibly improves firmness, fades dark spots, and brightens dull skin.
-Ferulic Acid and Vitamin E: Enhance the benefits of vitamin C while protecting skin from environmental damage.
-Hyaluronic Acid (Sodium Hyaluronate): Helps skin retain hydration while reducing the appearance of fine lines and wrinkles.

Water (Aqua), Ascorbic Acid, Butylene Glycol, Ethoxydiglycol, Glycerin, PPG-26-Buteth-26, PEG-40 Hydrogenated Castor Oil, Pentylene Glycol, Tocopherol (Vitamin E), Sodium Hyaluronate, Hexanoyl Dipeptide-3 Norleucine Acetate, Lecithin, Ferulic Acid, Panthenol, Bisabolol, Oryza Sativa (Rice) Bran Extract, Propyl Gallate, Sodium Gluconate, Sodium Hydroxide, Phenoxyethanol, Ethylhexylglycerin.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A high-strength serum with 15 percent pure vitamin C to visibly improve skin’s brightness, firmness, stubborn discoloration, and dull and uneven tone.</p>
<p><b>Skin Type:</b> Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><b>Skincare Concerns:</b> Dark Spots, Fine Lines and Wrinkles, and Dullness</p>
<p><b>Formulation:</b> Liquid</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Vitamin C (L-Ascorbic Acid) 15%: Visibly improves firmness, fades dark spots, and brightens dull skin.<br />
&#8211; Ferulic Acid and Vitamin E: Enhance the benefits of vitamin C while protecting skin from environmental damage.<br />
&#8211; Hyaluronic Acid (Sodium Hyaluronate): Helps skin retain hydration while reducing the appearance of fine lines and wrinkles.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, sulfates SLS &amp; SLES, triclocarban, and triclosan. It is also cruelty-free and comes in recyclable packaging.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> Formulated at an ideal pH level of three and featuring 15 percent stabilized L-ascorbic acid, vitamin E, ferulic acid, hyaluronic acid, and a targeted peptide, this concentrated serum fades the look of sun damage and post-breakout marks while visibly addressing dullness and loss of firmness for a luminously healthy look.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/c15-vitamin-c-super-booster/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>RESIST Advanced Replenishing Toner with Hyaluronic Acid</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/resist-advanced-replenishing-toner-with-hyaluronic-acid/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/resist-advanced-replenishing-toner-with-hyaluronic-acid/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=529</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Hyaluronic Acid: Helps skin retain lasting hydration and reduces the look of fine lines and wrinkles.
-Linoleic, Oleic, and Linolenic Acids: Visibly diminish dullness and support skin's resilience.
-Evening Primrose Oil: An antioxidant-rich, non-fragrant plant oil that rapidly replenishes moisture.

Water (Aqua), Cyclopentasiloxane, Glycerin, Glycerth-26, Polysorbate 20, Dimethiconol, Linoleic Acid, Oleic Acid, Linolenic Acid, Phospholipids, Carnosine, Epigallocatechin Gallate, Genistein, Sodium Hyaluronate, Sphingolipids, Ferulic Acid, Laurdimonium Hydroxypropyl Hydrolyzed Soy Protein, Glycyrrhiza Glabra (Licorice) Root Extract, Acetyl Glucosamine, Quercetin, Oenothera Biennis (Evening Primrose) Oil, Beta Vulgaris (Beet) Root Extract, Cucurbita Pepo (Pumpkin) Seed Extract, Lecithin, Caprylic/Capric Triglyceride, Hydrolyzed Corn Starch, Hydrogenated Lecithin, Palmitic Acid, Butylene Glycol, Acrylates/C10-30 Alkyl Acrylate Crosspolymer, Xanthan Gum, Laureth-23, Laureth-4, Aminomethyl Propanol, Disodium EDTA, Sodium Benzoate, Ethylhexylglycerin, Phenoxyethanol, Chlorphenesin, Benzoic Acid, Sorbic Acid.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A softening toner that replenishes essential nutrients, fatty acids, and hyaluronic acid to visibly plump and soothe your skin after cleansing.</p>
<p><b>Skin Type:</b> Normal and Dry</p>
<p><b>Skincare Concerns:</b> Fine Lines and Wrinkles, Dryness, and Dullness</p>
<p><b>Formulation:</b> Liquid</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Hyaluronic Acid: Helps skin retain lasting hydration and reduces the look of fine lines and wrinkles.<br />
&#8211; Linoleic, Oleic, and Linolenic Acids: Visibly diminish dullness and support skin&#8217;s resilience.<br />
&#8211; Evening Primrose Oil: An antioxidant-rich, non-fragrant plant oil that rapidly replenishes moisture.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, sulfates SLS &amp; SLES, triclocarban, triclosanand triclosan. It is also gluten-free, cruelty-free, and comes in recyclable packaging.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> This ultra-hydrating toner feels just like a comforting liquid lotion, enriching skin with essential omega fatty acids and plant-derived antioxidants to improve visible signs of aging and dehydration. Over time, it reinforces the skin’s vital moisture barrier and optimizes its ability to retain hydration.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/resist-advanced-replenishing-toner-with-hyaluronic-acid/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Skin Perfecting 2% BHA Liquid Exfoliant</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/skin-perfecting-2-bha-liquid-exfoliant/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/skin-perfecting-2-bha-liquid-exfoliant/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=450</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Salicylic Acid (BHA) 2%: Penetrates pores to clear blemish-causing buildup and shed dead skin.
-Green Tea: A potent antioxidant that soothes irritated skin while improving visible signs of aging.
-Methylpropanediol: Hydrates while visibly enhancing the skin’s glow and the formula’s penetration.

Water (Aqua), Methylpropanediol, Butylene Glycol, Salicylic Acid, Polysorbate 20, Camellia Oleifera (Green Tea) Leaf Extract, Sodium Hydroxide, Tetrasodium EDTA.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A daily leave-on exfoliant with two percent salicylic acid to sweep away dead skin cells, unclog pores, and visibly smooth wrinkles—practically overnight.</p>
<p><b>Skin Type:</b> Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><b>Skincare Concerns:</b> Pores, Uneven Texture, and Acne and Blemishes</p>
<p><b>Formulation:</b> Liquid</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Salicylic Acid (BHA) 2%: Penetrates pores to clear blemish-causing buildup and shed dead skin.<br />
&#8211; Green Tea: A potent antioxidant that soothes irritated skin while improving visible signs of aging.<br />
&#8211; Methylpropanediol: Hydrates while visibly enhancing the skin’s glow and the formula’s penetration.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, sulfates SLS &amp; SLES, triclocarban, and triclosan. It is also gluten-free, cruelty-free, and comes in recyclable packaging.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> With a two percent concentration of salicylic acid and a pH range of 3.2 to 3.8, this global bestseller breaks down complexion-dulling buildup on skin’s surface and within pores. It leaves skin feeling dramatically smoother and looking clearer and more radiant than before. People notice a natural, visible glow after just one use.</p>
<p><b>Clinical Results:</b> In an independent consumer panel:<br />
&#8211; 91% of users had visibly healthier skin<br />
&#8211; 90% saw improved skin texture<br />
&#8211; 82% experienced smaller-looking pores</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/skin-perfecting-2-bha-liquid-exfoliant/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
