<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cleansers &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<atom:link href="http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/danh-muc-san-pham/skincare/cleansers/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 13:02:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>vi</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/favicon.png</url>
	<title>Cleansers &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Green Tea Hyaluronic Acid Hydrating Toner</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/green-tea-hyaluronic-acid-hydrating-toner/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/green-tea-hyaluronic-acid-hydrating-toner/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 13:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=533</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-5 Types of Hyaluronic Acid: Provide more thorough, amplified hydration.
-Green Tea Tri-Biotics™: Hydrate and helps fortify skin’s moisture barrier.
-Panthenol: Helps nurture skin.
Water/Aqua/ Eau, Butylene Glycol, Propanediol, Glycerin, 1,2-Hexanediol, Trehalose, Panthenol, Polyglycerin-3, Ppg-13-Decyltetradeceth-24, Caprylic/Capric Triglyceride, Lactobacillus Ferment Lysate, Xanthan Gum, Ethylhexylglycerin, Fragrance/Parfum, Disodium Edta, Cellulose Gum, Camellia Sinensis Leaf Extract, Squalane, Camellia Sinensis Seed Oil, Lactic Acid, Linalool, Limonene, Sodium Hyaluronate, Hydrolyzed Hyaluronic Acid, Sodium Hyaluronate Crosspolymer, Hyaluronic Acid, Acrylates/Stearyl Methacrylate Copolymer, Tremella Fuciformis Sporocarp Extract, Sodium Acetylated Hyaluronate, Tocopherol, Ceramide Np.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A watery toner infused with green tea and hyaluronic acid to deliver thorough hydration and prep skin.<br />
<b>Skin Type:</b> Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><b>Skincare Concerns:</b> Dryness</p>
<p><b>Formulation:</b> Liquid</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; 5 Types of Hyaluronic Acid: Provide more thorough, amplified hydration.<br />
&#8211; Green Tea Tri-Biotics<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />: Hydrate and helps fortify skin’s moisture barrier.<br />
&#8211; Panthenol: Helps nurture skin.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, sulfates SLS &amp; SLES, triclocarban, triclosan, and contains less than one percent synthetic fragrance.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> This lightweight, moisturizing toner is packed with antioxidants and amino acids from a balanced blend of green tea extracts and skin-nourishing panthenol for a hydrated canvas, ready for the next steps in your skincare routine.</p>
<p><b>Clinical Results:</b> Based on a 2-week independent consumer study on 30 women ages 20 to 35:<br />
&#8211; 100% felt that the product applies smoothly<br />
&#8211; 96% felt skin was more hydrated<br />
&#8211; 93% felt that skin was soothed with hydration</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/green-tea-hyaluronic-acid-hydrating-toner/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Squalane Cleanser</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/squalane-cleanser/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/squalane-cleanser/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=531</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Squalane, Aqua (Water), Coco-Caprylate/Caprate, Glycerin, Sucrose Stearate, Ethyl Macadamiate, Caprylic/Capric Triglyceride, Sucrose Laurate, Hydrogenated Starch Hydrolysate, Sucrose Dilaurate, Sucrose Trilaurate, Polyacrylate Crosspolymer-6, Isoceteth-20, Sodium Polyacrylate, Tocopherol, Hydroxymethoxyphenyl Decanone, Trisodium Ethylenediamine Disuccinate, Malic Acid, Ethylhexylglycerin, Chlorphenesin.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A gentle, moisturizing facial cleanser.</p>
<p><b>Skin Type:</b> Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><b>Skincare Concerns:</b> Pores and Dryness</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, sulfates SLS &amp; SLES, triclocarban, triclosan, and contains less than one percent synthetic fragrance. It is also vegan, gluten-free, and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> This gentle cleansing product is formulated to target makeup removal while leaving the skin feeling smooth and moisturized.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/squalane-cleanser/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>RESIST Advanced Replenishing Toner with Hyaluronic Acid</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/resist-advanced-replenishing-toner-with-hyaluronic-acid/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/resist-advanced-replenishing-toner-with-hyaluronic-acid/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=529</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Hyaluronic Acid: Helps skin retain lasting hydration and reduces the look of fine lines and wrinkles.
-Linoleic, Oleic, and Linolenic Acids: Visibly diminish dullness and support skin's resilience.
-Evening Primrose Oil: An antioxidant-rich, non-fragrant plant oil that rapidly replenishes moisture.

Water (Aqua), Cyclopentasiloxane, Glycerin, Glycerth-26, Polysorbate 20, Dimethiconol, Linoleic Acid, Oleic Acid, Linolenic Acid, Phospholipids, Carnosine, Epigallocatechin Gallate, Genistein, Sodium Hyaluronate, Sphingolipids, Ferulic Acid, Laurdimonium Hydroxypropyl Hydrolyzed Soy Protein, Glycyrrhiza Glabra (Licorice) Root Extract, Acetyl Glucosamine, Quercetin, Oenothera Biennis (Evening Primrose) Oil, Beta Vulgaris (Beet) Root Extract, Cucurbita Pepo (Pumpkin) Seed Extract, Lecithin, Caprylic/Capric Triglyceride, Hydrolyzed Corn Starch, Hydrogenated Lecithin, Palmitic Acid, Butylene Glycol, Acrylates/C10-30 Alkyl Acrylate Crosspolymer, Xanthan Gum, Laureth-23, Laureth-4, Aminomethyl Propanol, Disodium EDTA, Sodium Benzoate, Ethylhexylglycerin, Phenoxyethanol, Chlorphenesin, Benzoic Acid, Sorbic Acid.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A softening toner that replenishes essential nutrients, fatty acids, and hyaluronic acid to visibly plump and soothe your skin after cleansing.</p>
<p><b>Skin Type:</b> Normal and Dry</p>
<p><b>Skincare Concerns:</b> Fine Lines and Wrinkles, Dryness, and Dullness</p>
<p><b>Formulation:</b> Liquid</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Hyaluronic Acid: Helps skin retain lasting hydration and reduces the look of fine lines and wrinkles.<br />
&#8211; Linoleic, Oleic, and Linolenic Acids: Visibly diminish dullness and support skin&#8217;s resilience.<br />
&#8211; Evening Primrose Oil: An antioxidant-rich, non-fragrant plant oil that rapidly replenishes moisture.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, sulfates SLS &amp; SLES, triclocarban, triclosanand triclosan. It is also gluten-free, cruelty-free, and comes in recyclable packaging.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> This ultra-hydrating toner feels just like a comforting liquid lotion, enriching skin with essential omega fatty acids and plant-derived antioxidants to improve visible signs of aging and dehydration. Over time, it reinforces the skin’s vital moisture barrier and optimizes its ability to retain hydration.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/resist-advanced-replenishing-toner-with-hyaluronic-acid/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ceramidin™ Skin Barrier Serum Toner</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/ceramidin-skin-barrier-serum-toner/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/ceramidin-skin-barrier-serum-toner/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=527</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Ceramide NP: Supports the skin barrier.
-Panthenol: Moisturizes and nourishes skin’s barrier to prevent water loss.

Water/Aqua/Eau, Dipropylene Glycol, Betaine, Propanediol, Alcohol Denat., Glycosyl Trehalose, Glycerin, 1,2-Hexanediol, Panthenol, Pentylene Glycol, Erythritol, Hydrogenated Starch Hydrolysate, Triethylhexanoin, Diphenyl Dimethicone, Polyglyceryl-10 Myristate, Ceramide Np, Sucrose Distearate, Ethylhexylglycerin, Sodium Hyaluronate, Theobroma Cacao (Cocoa) Seed Extract, Pelargonium Graveolens Flower Oil, Olea Europaea (Olive) Fruit Oil, Citrus Aurantium Bergamia (Bergamot) Fruit Oil, C12-14 Pareth-12, Hydrogenated Lecithin, Acrylates/C10-30 Alkyl Acrylate Crosspolymer, Tromethamine, Carbomer, Glyceryl Polymethacrylate, Glyceryl Stearate, Dextrin, Salvia Officinalis (Sage) Oil, Citronellol, Disodium Edta, Yellow 5 (Ci 19140).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A serum and toner that supports the skin barrier, moisturizes, softens, tones, and preps skin for the next step.</p>
<p><b>Skin Type:</b> Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><b>Skincare Concerns:</b> Dryness, Dullness, and Uneven Texture</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Ceramide NP: Supports the skin barrier.<br />
&#8211; Panthenol: Moisturizes and nourishes skin’s barrier to prevent water loss.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> This rich liquid combines your serum and toner step for one, potent skincare essential. As a serum, it glides on to form a moisturizing base layer that supports the skin barrier. As a toner, it removes residue and visibly refines skin’s texture. This serum toner is loaded with barrier-supporting ceramide NP and panthenol for moisture and barrier reinforcement.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/ceramidin-skin-barrier-serum-toner/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Glycolic Acid 7% Exfoliating Toning Solution</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/glycolic-acid-7-exfoliating-toning-solution/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/glycolic-acid-7-exfoliating-toning-solution/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=454</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Glycolic Acid: An alpha hydroxy acid that exfoliates the skin.
-Tasmanian Pepperberry Derivative: Helps reduce irritation associated with acid use.
-Ginseng Root and Aloe Vera: Offer both visible radiance and soothing benefits.

Aqua (Water), Glycolic Acid, Rosa damascena flower water, Centaurea cyanus flower water, Aloe Barbadensis Leaf Water, Propanediol, Glycerin, Triethanolamine, Aminomethyl Propanol, Panax Ginseng Root Extract, Tasmannia Lanceolata Fruit/Leaf Extract, Aspartic Acid, Alanine, Glycine, Serine, Valine, Isoleucine, Proline, Threonine, Histidine, Phenylalanine, Glutamic Acid, Arginine, PCA, Sodium PCA, Sodium Lactate, Fructose, Glucose, Sucrose, Urea, Hexyl Nicotinate, Dextrin, Citric Acid, Polysorbate 20, Gellan Gum, Trisodium Ethylenediamine Disuccinate, Sodium Chloride, Hexylene Glycol, Potassium Sorbate, Sodium Benzoate, 1,2-Hexanediol, Caprylyl Glycol.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>An exfoliating toning solution with seven percent glycolic acid, amino acids, aloe vera, ginseng, and Tasmanian pepperberry.</p>
<p><b>Skin Type:</b> Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><b>Skincare Concerns:</b> Dullness and Uneven Texture</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Glycolic Acid: An alpha hydroxy acid that exfoliates the skin.<br />
&#8211; Tasmanian Pepperberry Derivative: Helps reduce irritation associated with acid use.<br />
&#8211; Ginseng Root and Aloe Vera: Offer both visible radiance and soothing benefits.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, phthalates, mineral oil, oxybenzone, coal tar, and sulfates SLS &amp; SLES. It is also vegan, gluten-free, and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> This 7% Toning Solution offers mild exfoliation for visibly improved skin radiance and clarity. The formula also improves the appearance of skin texture with continued use. This product is vegan, cruelty-free, and formulated without oil, alcohol, silicone, nuts, gluten, and fragrance.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/glycolic-acid-7-exfoliating-toning-solution/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Precleanse Cleansing Oil</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/precleanse-cleansing-oil/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/precleanse-cleansing-oil/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=452</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Vitamin E: Nourishes and protects skin from damage.
-Rice Bran: Gently exfoliates.
-Rosemary: Protects skin from damage.

Caprylic/Capric Triglycerides, Prunus Armeniaca (Apricot) Kernel Oil, PEG-40 Sorbitan Peroleate, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Oil, Citrus Aurantium Dulcis (Orange) Oil, Citrus Grandis (Grapefruit) Peel Oil, Cymbopogon Schoenanthus Oil, Borago Officinalis Seed Oil, Lavandula Angustifolia (Lavender) Oil, Rosmarinus Officinalis (Rosemary) Leaf Extract, Solanum Lycopersicum (Tomato) Extract, Lavandula Hybrida Oil, Citrus Nobilis (Mandarin Orange) Peel Oil, Oryza Sativa (Rice) Bran Oil, Carthamus Tinctorius (Safflower) Seed Oil, Aleurites Moluccana Seed Oil, Cetyl Ethylhexanoate, Dicaprylyl Carbonate, Tocopheryl Acetate, Tocopherol, C12-15 Alkyl Benzoate, Citral, Limonene, Linalool.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A thoroughly cleansing oil that melts away waterproof makeup, SPF, debris, and oil without clogging pores or stripping your skin’s natural oils.</p>
<p><b>Skin Type:</b> Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><b>Skincare Concerns:</b> Pores, Redness, and Acne and Blemishes</p>
<p><b>Formulation:</b> Lightweight Oil</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Vitamin E and Rice Bran Extract: Antioxidant-rich ingredients that moisturize, smooth, and soften skin.<br />
&#8211; Kukui Nut Oil and Borage Seed Oil: Supply vitamins A and C, as well as skin-barrier-supportive omega-3 fatty acids.<br />
&#8211; Apricot Kernel Oil: Soothes irritated skin, nourishes, and moisturizes.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, sulfates SLS &amp; SLES, triclocarban, triclosan, and contains less than one percent synthetic fragrance. It is also vegan, gluten-free, and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> An iconic formula from the brand known for the double cleanse, the Precleanse Cleansing Oil is a blend of lightweight plant-based oils that melt away layers of sebum (oil), SPF, waterproof makeup, and other impurities that build up on skin throughout the day. Gentle enough for the eyes, this formula will even remove eyelash glue.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/precleanse-cleansing-oil/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Skin Perfecting 2% BHA Liquid Exfoliant</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/skin-perfecting-2-bha-liquid-exfoliant/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/skin-perfecting-2-bha-liquid-exfoliant/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=450</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Salicylic Acid (BHA) 2%: Penetrates pores to clear blemish-causing buildup and shed dead skin.
-Green Tea: A potent antioxidant that soothes irritated skin while improving visible signs of aging.
-Methylpropanediol: Hydrates while visibly enhancing the skin’s glow and the formula’s penetration.

Water (Aqua), Methylpropanediol, Butylene Glycol, Salicylic Acid, Polysorbate 20, Camellia Oleifera (Green Tea) Leaf Extract, Sodium Hydroxide, Tetrasodium EDTA.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A daily leave-on exfoliant with two percent salicylic acid to sweep away dead skin cells, unclog pores, and visibly smooth wrinkles—practically overnight.</p>
<p><b>Skin Type:</b> Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><b>Skincare Concerns:</b> Pores, Uneven Texture, and Acne and Blemishes</p>
<p><b>Formulation:</b> Liquid</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Salicylic Acid (BHA) 2%: Penetrates pores to clear blemish-causing buildup and shed dead skin.<br />
&#8211; Green Tea: A potent antioxidant that soothes irritated skin while improving visible signs of aging.<br />
&#8211; Methylpropanediol: Hydrates while visibly enhancing the skin’s glow and the formula’s penetration.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, sulfates SLS &amp; SLES, triclocarban, and triclosan. It is also gluten-free, cruelty-free, and comes in recyclable packaging.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> With a two percent concentration of salicylic acid and a pH range of 3.2 to 3.8, this global bestseller breaks down complexion-dulling buildup on skin’s surface and within pores. It leaves skin feeling dramatically smoother and looking clearer and more radiant than before. People notice a natural, visible glow after just one use.</p>
<p><b>Clinical Results:</b> In an independent consumer panel:<br />
&#8211; 91% of users had visibly healthier skin<br />
&#8211; 90% saw improved skin texture<br />
&#8211; 82% experienced smaller-looking pores</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/skin-perfecting-2-bha-liquid-exfoliant/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ultra Facial Cleanser</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/ultra-facial-cleanser/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/ultra-facial-cleanser/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=448</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Water, Sodium Laureth Sulfate, Decyl Glucoside, Glycerin, Cocamidopropyl Betaine, Disodium Cocoamphodiacetate, Acrylates Copolymer, PEG-200 Hydrogenated Glyceryl Palmate, Lauryl Glucoside, Sodium Chloride, Pentylene Glycol, Triethanolamine, Phenoxyethanol, PEG-7 Glyceryl Cocoate, Distearyl Ether, Behenyl Alcohol, Methylparaben, Laureth-2, Propylparaben, Sodium Methylparaben, Squalane, Prunus Amygdalus Dulcis Oil/Sweet Almond Oil, Prunus Armeniaca Kernel Oil/Apricot Kernel Oil, Tocopherol, Ascorbyl Glucoside, Persea Gratissima Oil/Avocado Oil, Sodium Hydroxide, Citric Acid.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A foaming cleanser formulated to help remove excess oil, dirt, and debris.</p>
<p><b>Skin Type: </b>Normal, Dry, Sensitive</p>
<p><b>Skincare Concerns: </b>Oiliness, Dullness and Uneven Texture, and Acne and Blemishes</p>
<p><b>Formulation: </b>Lightweight Gel</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:</b><br />
&#8211; Apricot Kernel Oil: Moisturizes and softens skin while helping retain clarity and suppleness.<br />
&#8211; Avocado Oil: Helps to restore the natural moisture of the skin.<br />
&#8211; Squalane (Perhydrosqualene or Perhydrosqualene Vegetal): Is easily absorbed and helps restore skin’s natural moisture balance to keep it extra soft and supple.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know: </b>This gentle face wash helps lift away dirt and excess oil without over-drying skin. With emollients like apricot kernel oil, avocado oil, and squalane, this liquid formula cleanses skin gently without stripping it of its natural oils.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/ultra-facial-cleanser/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
