<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Face &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<atom:link href="http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/danh-muc-san-pham/makeup/face/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 13:11:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>vi</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/favicon.png</url>
	<title>Face &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Killawatt Freestyle Highlighter</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/killawatt-freestyle-highlighter/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/killawatt-freestyle-highlighter/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=525</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<b>Ginger Binge:</b>
Dimethicone, Talc, Isododecane, Synthetic Fluorphlogopite, Caprylic/Capric Triglyceride, Phenoxyethanol, Tin Oxide, Bismuth Oxychloride (CI 77163), Titanium Dioxide (CI 77891), Iron Oxides (CI 77491), Carmine (CI 75470), Yellow 5 Lake (CI 19140).

<b>Moscow Mule:</b>
Dimethicone, Synthetic Fluorphlogopite, Isododecane, Diisostearyl Malate, Polyethylene, Aluminum Calcium Sodium Silicate, Talc, Cetyl Dimethicone, Phenoxyethanol, Tin Oxide, Calcium Aluminum Borosilicate, Silica, Calcium Sodium Borosilicate, Titanium Dioxide (CI 77891), Bismuth Oxychloride (CI 77163), Manganese Violet (CI 77742), Iron Oxides (CI 77491, CI 77492), Carmine (CI 75470), Yellow 5 Lake (CI 19140).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A weightless, long-wear, cream-powder hybrid highlighter for the face and eyes in a range of shades, from subtle to supercharged, in solos and expertly-paired duos.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens and phthalates. This product is also cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> This long-wearing highlighter was born in a lineup of solos and duos for all skin tones. The cream-powder hybrid melts into skin and blends with almost zero effort. Loaded with superfine shimmer for an ultra-smooth, creamy texture, it’s your go-to for highlighting your face, eyes, and collarbone.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/killawatt-freestyle-highlighter/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eaze Drop Blurring Skin Tint</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/eaze-drop-blurring-skin-tint/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/eaze-drop-blurring-skin-tint/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:52:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=523</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Aqua/Water/Eau, Dimethicone, Dicaprylyl Carbonate, Talc, Isostearyl Neopentanoate, Peg-10 Dimethicone, Dimethicone/Vinyl Dimethicone Crosspolymer, Glycerin, Trimethylsiloxysilicate, Isododecane, Bis-Peg/Ppg-14/14 Dimethicone, Phenoxyethanol, Sodium Chloride, Dimethicone Crosspolymer, Magnesium Sulfate, Hydrogen Dimethicone, Sodium Dehydroacetate, Trehalose, Urea, Potassium Sorbate, Silica, Disteardimonium Hectorite, Aluminum Hydroxide, Benzoic Acid, Sodium Hyaluronate, C24-28 Alkyl Methicone, Pentylene Glycol, Serine, Dehydroacetic Acid, Propylene Carbonate, Ethylhexylglycerin, Algin, Caprylyl Glycol, Disodium Phosphate, Glyceryl Polyacrylate, Pullulan, Tocopherol, Potassium Phosphate, Iron Oxides (Ci 77491, Ci 77492, Ci 77499), Titanium Dioxide (Ci 77891).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>What it is: </strong>A lightweight, buildable light-to-medium coverage tinted moisturizer that leaves skin looking blurred and smoothed—In 25 flexible shades for all.</p>
<p><strong>Coverage: </strong>Light</p>
<p><strong>Finish: </strong>Natural</p>
<p><strong>Formulation: </strong>Liquid</p>
<p><strong>Ingredient Callouts:</strong> Free of parabens and phthalates. It is also vegan, gluten-free, and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><strong>What Else You Need to Know: </strong>This is an easy-to-apply, flexible skin tint Rihanna wanted to create. This tinted moisturizer quickly and visibly evens out complexion with a blurred effect. The HydraBlend complex and humidity-, sweat-, and transfer-resistant formula has a smooth texture that layers well with primer and skincare.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/eaze-drop-blurring-skin-tint/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Light Reflecting Advanced Skincare Foundation</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/light-reflecting-advanced-skincare-foundation/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/light-reflecting-advanced-skincare-foundation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=520</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Biomimetic Oat: Visibly improves clarity by reducing the appearance of redness.
-Japanese Lilyturf: Supports a strong skin barrier by helping maintain moisture.
-Cacao Peptides and Milk Thistle: Minimize the negative effect of blue light and environmental stressors.

Water/Aqua/Eau, C9-12 Alkane, Butylene Glycol, Undecane, Tridecane, Isodecyl Neopentanoate, Hydrogenated Polyisobutene, Polyglyceryl-6 Polyricinoleate, Polyglyceryl-2 Diisostearate, Disteardimonium Hectorite, Diisostearyl Malate, Glycerin, Synthetic Wax, Sodium Chloride, Ophiopogon Japonicus Root Extract, Ascophyllum Nodosum Extract, Theobroma Cacao (Cocoa) Seed Extract, Curcuma Longa (Turmeric) Root Extract, Silybum Marianum Fruit Extract, Aluminum Hydroxide, Magnesium Chloride, Sodium Dilauramidoglutamide Lysine, Tocopherol, Coco-Caprylate/Caprate, Ethylhexylglycerin, Pentylene Glycol, Hydroxyphenyl Propamidobenzoic Acid, Ascorbyl Palmitate, Citric Acid, Sea Water/Maris Aqua/Eau De Mer, Trisodium EDTA, Barium Sulfate, Alumina, Chlorphenesin, Phenoxyethanol, Potassium Sorbate, [+/-(May Contain/Peut Contenir): Iron Oxides (CI 77491, CI 77492, CI 77499), Mica, Titanium Dioxide (CI 77891)].]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>An advanced makeup-skincare-hybrid foundation with a natural finish that quickly blurs and smooths while visibly improving skin’s clarity over time.</p>
<p><b>Coverage: </b>Medium<br />
<b><br />
Finish: </b>Natural<br />
<b><br />
Formulation: </b>Liquid<br />
<b><br />
Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Biomimetic Oat: Visibly improves clarity by reducing the appearance of redness.<br />
&#8211; Japanese Lilyturf: Supports a strong skin barrier by helping maintain moisture.<br />
&#8211; Cacao Peptides and Milk Thistle: Minimize the negative effect of blue light and environmental stressors.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, sulfates SLS &amp; SLES, triclocarban, triclosan, and contains less than one percent synthetic fragrance. It is also vegan and comes in recyclable packaging.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> This breathable, medium-coverage, buildable foundation quickly conceals visible redness, blemishes, and dark spots while blurring the look of wrinkles, pores, and texture. Powered by 70 percent-skincare ingredients for visibly improved clarity plus Light Reflecting Complex for enhanced luminosity, the up to all-day-wear formula is suitable for most skin types, including sensitive.</p>
<p><b>Clinical Results:</b> In a clinical study of 31 women immediately after application:<br />
&#8211; It revealed a more even-looking skin tone by +93%</p>
<p>In a 6-week clinical study of 31 women:<br />
&#8211; It improved the appearance of skin clarity over time, even after makeup was removed</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/light-reflecting-advanced-skincare-foundation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Soft Matte Complete Concealer</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/soft-matte-complete-concealer/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/soft-matte-complete-concealer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:49:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=518</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dimethicone, Water, Glycerin, Butylene Glycol, Nylon-12, Paraffin, Dimethicone/Vinyl Dimethicone Crosspolymer, Dicaprylyl Carbonate, Zinc Oxide, Peg-10 Dimethicone, Peg-400, Sorbitan Sesquiisostearate, Microcrystalline Wax/Cera Microcristallina, Aluminum Hydroxide, Phenoxyethanol, Polysilicone-2, Silica, Barium Sulfate, Dextrin Palmitate, Distearyldimonium Chloride, Palmitic Acid, Hydrogen Dimethicone, Palmitoyl Tripeptide-5, Ascorbic Acid, Retinyl Palmitate, Tocopheryl Acetate, Alumina, Sodium Acetylated Hyaluronate, Tocopherol, [+/- (May Contain): Mica, Titanium Dioxide (Ci 77891), Iron Oxides (Ci 77491), Iron Oxides (Ci 77492), Iron Oxides (Ci 77499)].]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A full-coverage, oil-free concealer that conceals and blurs imperfections with a soft-matte, natural-looking finish.</p>
<p><b>Coverage:</b> Full</p>
<p><b>Finish:</b> Matte</p>
<p><b>Formulation:</b> Cream</p>
<p><b>Skin Type:</b> Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:</b><br />
&#8211; Peptides: Reduce appearance of wrinkles and pores over time.<br />
&#8211; Hyaluronic Acid: Reduce appearance of wrinkles and pores.<br />
&#8211; Antioxidants (Vitamins A, C, and E): Deliver Daily Defense.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of sulfates SLS and SLES, parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, oil, mineral oil, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, triclosan, and triclocarban, and contains less than one percent of synthetic fragrances. This product is also vegan and gluten-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> NARS’s Soft-Focus Smoothing Complex contains Optimal Diffusion Powder, which transforms the look of skin by blurring imperfections with light-diffusing spheres. The formula delivers all-day wear and high coverage that’s non-cakey, and won’t settle into fine lines and pores.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/soft-matte-complete-concealer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Diamond Bomb All-Over Diamond Veil</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/diamond-bomb-all-over-diamond-veil/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/diamond-bomb-all-over-diamond-veil/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:47:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=516</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polymethylsilsesquioxane, Phenyl Trimethicone, Calcium Sodium Borosilicate, Diisostearyl Malate, Dimethicone, Calcium Aluminum Borosilicate, Mica, Dimethicone/Vinyl Dimethicone Crosspolymer, Pentylene Glycol, Tin Oxide, Aqua/Water/Eau, Triethoxycaprylylsilane, Polyisobutene, Iron Oxides (Ci 77491), Titanium Dioxide (Ci 77891), Carmine (Ci 75470).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A diamond-dusted highlighter that delivers a 3D glittering veil of pure sparkle for face and body.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of sulfates SLS and SLES, parabens, and phthalates. This product is also gluten-free and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> Diamond Bomb has a 3D formula that’ll leave your face and body crystal-coated. It features a unique jelly-powder formula that’s cool to the touch, melts into skin, and creates an all-glitz-no-grit finish for all skin tones. Plus, it comes in a jewel-like compact you’ll never want to put down.</p>
<p>Diamond Bomb All-Over Diamond Veil was inspired by the crystal dress Rihanna wore at CFDA 2014.</p>
<p>&#8220;You can never have enough diamonds! This is the closest thing to bathing in it. The sparkle in this is just insane!&#8221;—Rihanna</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/diamond-bomb-all-over-diamond-veil/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Positive Light Liquid Luminizer Highlight</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/positive-light-liquid-luminizer-highlight/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/positive-light-liquid-luminizer-highlight/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=479</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Isododecane, Mica, Hydrogenated Polyisobutene, Hydrogenated Olive Oil Unsaponifiables, Hydrogenated Styrene/Isoprene Copolymer, Octyldodecanol, Dimethicone, Gardenia Florida Fruit Extract, Nelumbo Nucifera (Sacred Lotus) Flower Extract, Nymphaea Odorata Root Extract, Polyhydroxystearic Acid, Caprylic/Capric Triglyceride, Isostearic Acid, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Oil, Tin Oxide, Lecithin, Polyglyceryl-3 Polyricinoleate, Pentaerythrityl Tetra-di-t-butyl Hydroxyhydrocinnamate, [+/- May Contain: Titanium Dioxide (CI 77891), Iron Oxides (CI 77491, CI 77499)].]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A silky, second-skin liquid highlighter that creates a lasting, soft, and luminous finish.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of sulfates SLS and SLES, parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, triclosan, and triclocarban, and contains less than one percent of synthetic fragrances. This product is also vegan and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> Packed with light-reflecting pearl particles and a botanical blend of lotus, gardenia, and white waterlily, this multidimensional formula lends skin a dewy glow in seconds. Mix this weightless liquid highlighter with foundation or layer it across the high points of the face for instant radiance.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/positive-light-liquid-luminizer-highlight/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Always an Optimist Soft Radiance Setting Powder</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/always-an-optimist-soft-radiance-setting-powder/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/always-an-optimist-soft-radiance-setting-powder/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=477</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Mica, Calcium Carbonate, Silica, C12-15 Alkyl Benzoate, Magnesium Myristate, Nylon-12, 1,2-Hexanediol, Caprylic/Capric Triglyceride, Caprylyl Glycol, Coco-Caprylate/Caprate, Ethylhexylglycerin, Magnesium Stearate, Polymethylsilsesquioxane, Squalane, Tocopherol, Tocopheryl Acetate, Phenoxyethanol, [+/- May Contain/Peut Contenir: Iron Oxides (CI 77492, CI 77491, CI 77499), Yellow 5 Lake (CI 19140)].]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A silky, do-it-all, talc-free loose setting powder to visibly smooth, blur, and control shine for a soft natural finish and all-day comfort.<br />
<b><br />
Coverage: </b>Light<br />
<b><br />
Finish: </b>Natural<br />
<b><br />
Formulation: </b>Loose Powder</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, and contains less than one percent synthetic fragrance. It is also vegan and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> Super-finely milled and silky to the touch, this powder goes on light and airy to provide sheer, seamless coverage with a subtle but visible radiance and a natural finish. Extend makeup wear, blur the look of pores, and smooth skin’s texture. The custom-designed sifter locks for mess-free storage on the go.</p>
<p><b>Clinical Results:</b><br />
REAL RESULTS<br />
100% said it doesn’t look cakey or chalky<br />
100% said it layers well and doesn’t disturb makeup<br />
98% said it blurs and smooths the look of pores<br />
*In an independent consumer perception study of 50 subjects</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/always-an-optimist-soft-radiance-setting-powder/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pore Diffusing Primer &#8211; Always an Optimist Collection</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/pore-diffusing-primer-always-an-optimist-collection/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/pore-diffusing-primer-always-an-optimist-collection/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=476</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Hyaluronic Acid: Hydrates and conditions.
-Green Tea Extract: Helps soothe and calm skin.
-Vitamin E: Protects skin from environmental stressors.

Water/Aqua/Eau, Dimethicone, Methyl Trimethicone, Dipropylene Glycol, Glycerin, Butylene Glycol, Vinyl Dimethicone/Methicone Silsesquioxane Crosspolymer, Dimethicone/Vinyl Dimethicone Crosspolymer, Cetyl PEG/PPG-10/1 Dimethicone, Sodium Chloride, Dimethicone/PEG-10/15 Crosspolymer, Silica, Propanediol, Sodium Benzoate, Potassium Sorbate, Tocopheryl Acetate, Eclipta Prostrata Extract, Glyceryl Acrylate/Acrylic Acid Copolymer, Fragrance/Parfum, Camellia Sinensis Leaf Extract, Sodium Citrate, Melia Azadirachta Leaf Extract, Hyaluronic Acid, Hydrolyzed Hyaluronic Acid, Sodium Hyaluronate, Gardenia Florida Fruit Extract, Nelumbo Nucifera Flower Extract, Nymphaea Odorata Root Extract, Moringa Oleifera Seed Oil, Tocopherol.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A hydrating, cushiony gel primer that blurs the look of pores and fine lines, boosts and extends makeup wear, and helps fight shine all day.<b></b></p>
<p>Skin Type: Normal, Oily, Dry, Combination</p>
<p><b>Concerns: </b>Oil and Pores<b></b></p>
<p>Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
&#8211; Hyaluronic Acid: Hydrates and conditions.<br />
&#8211; Green Tea Extract: Helps soothe and calm skin.<br />
&#8211; Vitamin E: Protects skin from environmental stressors.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, and retinyl palmitate. It is also vegan and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> Great alone or under makeup, this lightweight, plush gel primer helps absorb shine, visibly evens out skin texture, and smooths away the look of pores quickly with a soft-focus effect. It is made with hyaluronic acid and also soothes while providing lasting hydration, so skin stays comfortable all day under makeup.</p>
<p><b>Clinical Results:</b> In an independent consumer study of 65 women:<br />
&#8211; 100% said it minimizes and smooths away the look of pores<br />
&#8211; 100% said it helps fight shine and extends foundation wear all day<br />
&#8211; 98% said it blurs the look of fine lines</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/pore-diffusing-primer-always-an-optimist-collection/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Positive Light Tinted Moisturizer Broad Spectrum SPF 20 Sunscreen</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/positive-light-tinted-moisturizer-broad-spectrum-spf-20-sunscreen/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/positive-light-tinted-moisturizer-broad-spectrum-spf-20-sunscreen/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=475</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Homosalate: 9.0%, Titanium Dioxide: 1.8%, Zinc Oxide: 0.9%, Water/Aqua, Dimethicone, Talc, C12-15 Alkyl Benzoate, Isododecane, Cetyl PEG/PPG-10/1 Dimethicone, Isopentyldiol, Sorbitol, Tocopheryl Acetate, Phenoxyethanol, Sodium Chloride, Dimethicone/Vinyl Dimethicone Crosspolymer, Magnesium Sulfate, Sodium Dehydroacetate, Hydrogen Dimethicone, Potassium Sorbate, Disteardimonium Hectorite, Lecithin, Benzoic Acid, Aluminum Hydroxide, Alumina, Dehydroacetic Acid, Propylene Carbonate, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Oil, Triethoxycaprylylsilane, Tocopherol, Ethylhexylglycerin, Ascorbyl Palmitate, Citric Acid, Gardenia Florida Fruit Extract, Nelumbo Nucifera Flower Extract, Nymphaea Odorata Root Extract, Titanium Dioxide (CI 77891), Iron Oxides (CI 77491, CI 77492, CI 77499).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>What it is: </strong>A flexible tinted moisturizer that immediately blurs skin with glowy, light to medium coverage, all while hydrating and protecting skin from the sun.</p>
<p><strong>Coverage: </strong>Light</p>
<p><strong>Finish: </strong>Radiant</p>
<p><strong>Formulation: </strong>Liquid</p>
<p><strong>SPF: </strong>SPF 20 and under</p>
<p><strong>Ingredient Callouts:</strong> Free of parabens. It is also vegan and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><strong>What Else You Need to Know:</strong> Think no-makeup makeup in a bottle. This weightless, breathable, tinted formula blends like moisturizer into a blurred, hydrated, naturally radiant, and non-sticky finish that lasts. With built-in sun protection plus vitamin E, it moves with your skin, wearing evenly in 24 flexible shades. This tinted moisturizer is noncomedogenic.</p>
<p><strong>Clinical Results:</strong></p>
<p>In an independent consumer study of 53 people:</p>
<p>&#8211; 100% said it glides on smoothly</p>
<p>&#8211; 94% said it evens out skin tone with a natural-looking finish</p>
<p>&#8211; 92% said skin appears smoother and that it’s comfortable to wear all day</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/positive-light-tinted-moisturizer-broad-spectrum-spf-20-sunscreen/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Premium BB Tinted Moisturizer with Niacinamide and SPF 40</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/premium-bb-tinted-moisturizer-with-niacinamide-and-spf-40/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/premium-bb-tinted-moisturizer-with-niacinamide-and-spf-40/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=473</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Glycerin: Rapidly moisturizes.

-Mineral and Chemical Sunscreens: Deliver UV protection.

-Niacinamide: Supports skin-barrier strength and protects against environmental stressors.

WATER/AQUA/EAU, CYCLOPENTASILOXANE, CYCLOHEXASILOXANE, GLYCERIN, PEG-10 DIMETHICONE, TALC, HEXYL LAURATE, DIPROPYLENE GLYCOL, C12-15 ALKYL BENZOATE, NIACINAMIDE, DIPHENYLSILOXY PHENYL TRIMETHICONE, DISTEARDIMONIUM HECTORITE, CITRUS AURANTIUM BERGAMIA (BERGAMOT) FRUIT OIL, CITRUS LIMON (LEMON) PEEL OIL, CITRUS AURANTIFOLIA (LIME) OIL, PINUS SYLVESTRIS (PINE) LEAF OIL, CITRUS AURANTIUM DULCIS (ORANGE) PEEL OIL, ADENOSINE, ALLANTOIN, ETHYLHEXYLGLYCERIN, TRIHYDROXYSTEARIN, POLYGLYCERYL-6 POLYRICINOLEATE, METHICONE, DIMETHICONE,DIMETHICONE/VINYL DIMETHICONE CROSSPOLYMER, 1,2-HEXANEDIOL, TRIETHOXYCAPRYLYLSILANE, MAGNESIUM SULFATE, EUCALYPTUS GLOBULUS LEAF OIL, LIMONENE, TOCOPHEROL, BHT, PHENOXYETHANOL, TITANIUM DIOXIDE (CI 77891), IRON OXIDES (CI 77492), IRON OXIDES (CI 77491), IRON OXIDES (CI 77499) &#60;ILN50730&#62;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>What it is: </strong>A multitasking, niacinamide-powered cream with a natural-looking finish that hydrates, conceals, and protects.</p>
<p><strong>Coverage: </strong>Light</p>
<p><strong>Finish: </strong>Natural</p>
<p><strong>Formulation: </strong>Cream</p>
<p><strong>SPF: </strong>Over 30</p>
<p><strong>Highlighted Ingredients:</strong></p>
<p>&#8211; Glycerin: Rapidly moisturizes.</p>
<p>&#8211; Mineral and Chemical Sunscreens: Deliver UV protection.</p>
<p>&#8211; Niacinamide: Helps improve skin&#8217;s barrier</p>
<p><strong>What Else You Need to Know:</strong> It’s your moisturizer, your makeup and your sunscreen in one. This BB Cream with SPF 40 seamlessly spreads over skin to deliver lightweight coverage with a natural finish that looks like you. This color corrector comes in 4 flexible, easy-to-navigate shades that adapt to a range of skin tones.</p>
<p><strong>Clinical Results:</strong> In a 3-day consumer study of 114 participants:</p>
<p>&#8211; 96% said skin tone looks even</p>
<p>&#8211; 97% said skin feels moisturized</p>
<p>&#8211; 96% said it feels weightless on skin</p>
<p>&#8211; 97% said it didn’t leave a white cast</p>
<p>&#8211; 96% said skin looks smoother</p>
<p>&#8211; 97% said skin looks brighter</p>
<p>&#8211; 96% said it leaves a natural looks-like-me finish</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/premium-bb-tinted-moisturizer-with-niacinamide-and-spf-40/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
