<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Lip Plumper &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<atom:link href="http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/tu-khoa-san-pham/lip-plumper/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:36:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>vi</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/favicon.png</url>
	<title>Lip Plumper &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Dior Addict Lip Maximizer Plumping Gloss</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/dior-addict-lip-maximizer-plumping-gloss/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/dior-addict-lip-maximizer-plumping-gloss/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:36:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=509</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[001 Pink: #17318 Polyglyceryl-2 Triisostearate, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Oil, Hydrogenated Castor Oil Dimer Dilinoleate, Phytosteryl/Octyldodecyl Lauroyl Glutamate, Jojoba Esters, Polyglyceryl-2 Isostearate/Dimer Dilinoleate Copolymer, Candelilla Cera (Euphorbia Cerifera (Candelilla) Wax), Behenyl Behenate, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Wax, Butyrospermum Parkii (Shea) Butter, Oryza Sativa (Rice) Bran Wax, Caprylic/Capric Triglyceride, Parfum (Fragrance), Butyrospermum Parkii (Shea) Butter Unsaponifiables, Diisostearyl Malate, Prunus Avium (Sweet Cherry) Seed Oil, Trimethylolpropane Triisostearate, Tocopherol, Ethyl Vanillin, Ascorbyl Palmitate, Undaria Pinnatifida Extract, Propyl Gallate, [+/- Ci 77891 (Titanium Dioxide), Ci 77491, Ci 77499 (Iron Oxides), Ci 45380 (Red 21), Ci 15985 (Yellow 6 Lake), Ci 15850 (Red 7), Ci 42090 (Blue 1 Lake)]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>What it is: </strong>The iconic Dior Addict Lip Maximizer plumping lip gloss gets a refresh with a new 90% natural-origin formula, a reimagined case and updated shades.</p>
<p><strong>Ingredient Callouts:</strong> Free of sulfates SLS and SLES, parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, triclosan, and triclocarban, and contains less than one percent of synthetic fragrances. This product is also vegan, cruelty-free, and gluten-free, and comes in recyclable packaging.</p>
<p><strong>What Else You Need to Know:</strong> Composed of 90% natural-origin ingredients and infused with cherry oil and hyaluronic acid, this Dior plumping lip gloss smooths and makes lips look bigger, leaving them hydrated for up to 24h. Now available in a new range of shiny shades with clear, intense, shimmering and holographic finishes.</p>
<p><strong>Clinical Results:</strong> In a clinical test on 28 subjects:</p>
<p>&#8211; 36%+ immediate volume effect &#8211; 48%+ smoother lips In an instrumental test on 30 subjects: &#8211; 24h hydration 90% natural-origin ingredients: Amount calculated based on the ISO 16128-1 and ISO 16128-2 standard. Water percentage included. The remaining ingredients contribute to the formula’s performance, sensory appeal and stability.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/dior-addict-lip-maximizer-plumping-gloss/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gloss Bomb Heat Universal Lip Luminizer + Plumper</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/gloss-bomb-heat-universal-lip-luminizer-plumper/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/gloss-bomb-heat-universal-lip-luminizer-plumper/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=497</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Shea Butter
-Vitamin E

Polybutene, Octyldodecanol, Bis-Diglyceryl Polyacyladipate-2, Tricaprylin, Cera Microcristallina/Microcrystalline Wax/Cire Microcristalline, Hydrogenated Polyisobutene, Polyethylene, Silica Dimethyl Silylate, Butyrospermum Parkii (Shea) Butter, Vp/Eicosene Copolymer, Sorbitan Oleate, Vp/Hexadecene Copolymer, Synthetic Fluorphlogopite, Silica, Ethylhexyl Palmitate, Caprylyl Glycol, Aroma/Flavor, Parfum/Fragrance, Octyldodecyl Neopentanoate, Mica, Butyrospermum Parkii (Shea) Butter Unsaponifiables, Tribehenin, Pentaerythrityl Tetra-Di-T-Butyl Hydroxyhydrocinnamate, Methyl Nicotinate, Sorbitan Isostearate, Tocopherol, Tocopheryl Acetate, Vanillyl Butyl Ether, Capsicum Frutescens Fruit Extract, Glycine Soja (Soybean) Oil, Zingiber Officinale (Ginger) Root Oil, Tetrahexyldecyl Ascorbate, Lactic Acid, Calcium Sodium Borosilicate, Calcium Aluminum Borosilicate, Palmitoyl Tripeptide-1, Tin Oxide, Benzyl Benzoate, Limonene, Iron Oxides (Ci 77491), Titanium Dioxide (Ci 77891).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A lip luminizer and plumper that delivers a hint of tint and fuller-looking lips.<br />
<b><br />
Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Shea Butter<br />
&#8211; Vitamin E</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens and phthalates. It is also gluten-free and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> Gloss Bomb Heat has an innovative Plump Job Complex that contains a blend of ingredients designed to gently plump lips for an undeniably fuller pout. The conditioning shea butter and vitamin E help lock in moisture for an intense wet-look shine finish.</p>
<p><b>Clinical Results:</b> In a consumer study of 30 volunteers:<br />
&#8211; 96% agreed it feels nourishing and provides a high-shine finish<br />
&#8211; 93% agreed it feels conditioning<br />
&#8211; 93% agreed it has a lush texture and makes lips look smoother</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/gloss-bomb-heat-universal-lip-luminizer-plumper/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
