<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Lip &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<atom:link href="http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/danh-muc-san-pham/makeup/lip/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:39:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>vi</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/favicon.png</url>
	<title>Lip &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Kind Words Lip Liner</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/kind-words-lip-liner/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/kind-words-lip-liner/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=511</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Trimethylsiloxysilicate, Isohexadecane, Synthetic Wax, Mica, Isododecane, Ethylhexyl Palmitate, Microcrystalline Wax/Cera Microcristallina/Cire microcristalline, Polybutene, Silica, C13-15 Alkane, VP/Hexadecene Copolymer, Copernicia Cerifera (Carnauba) Wax/Copernicia Cerifera Cera/Cire de carnauba, Paraffin, Ethylene/Propylene Copolymer, Fragrance/Parfum, Caprylyl Glycol, Diisostearyl Malate, Gardenia Florida Fruit Extract, Glyceryl Caprylate, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Oil, Nelumbo Nucifera Flower Extract, Nymphaea Odorata Root Extract, Polyglyceryl-2 Diisostearate, Linalool. +/- (May Contain/Peut Contenir) Titanium Dioxide (CI 77891), Iron Oxides (CI 77491, CI 77492, CI 77499), Red 7 Lake (CI 15850).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A super creamy, waterproof lip liner that glides on like a balm to define lips—in the same 10 rich, made-to-match shades as the Kind Words Matte Lipstick.<b></p>
<p>Formulation Type: </b>Lip Liner</p>
<p><b>Benefits: </b>Hydrating and Long-wearing</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, sulfates SLS &amp; SLES, triclocarban, and triclosan. It is also vegan, cruelty-free, and comes in recyclable packaging.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> Define and shape lips with one-swipe color and a soft matte finish. With an incredibly smooth, balm-like glide that won’t skip or tug, this waterproof liner not only stays put all day without smudging, but it keeps your lipstick in place, too. Keep the retractable tip sharp with the built-in sharpener.</p>
<p><b>Clinical Results:</b> In an independent consumer study of 51 people:<br />
&#8211; 100% said it draws smooth, even lines<br />
&#8211; 100% said lips don’t feel dry and that it’s comfortable to wear<br />
&#8211; 100% said it helps prevent lipstick from feathering or bleeding</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/kind-words-lip-liner/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dior Addict Lip Maximizer Plumping Gloss</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/dior-addict-lip-maximizer-plumping-gloss/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/dior-addict-lip-maximizer-plumping-gloss/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:36:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=509</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[001 Pink: #17318 Polyglyceryl-2 Triisostearate, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Oil, Hydrogenated Castor Oil Dimer Dilinoleate, Phytosteryl/Octyldodecyl Lauroyl Glutamate, Jojoba Esters, Polyglyceryl-2 Isostearate/Dimer Dilinoleate Copolymer, Candelilla Cera (Euphorbia Cerifera (Candelilla) Wax), Behenyl Behenate, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Wax, Butyrospermum Parkii (Shea) Butter, Oryza Sativa (Rice) Bran Wax, Caprylic/Capric Triglyceride, Parfum (Fragrance), Butyrospermum Parkii (Shea) Butter Unsaponifiables, Diisostearyl Malate, Prunus Avium (Sweet Cherry) Seed Oil, Trimethylolpropane Triisostearate, Tocopherol, Ethyl Vanillin, Ascorbyl Palmitate, Undaria Pinnatifida Extract, Propyl Gallate, [+/- Ci 77891 (Titanium Dioxide), Ci 77491, Ci 77499 (Iron Oxides), Ci 45380 (Red 21), Ci 15985 (Yellow 6 Lake), Ci 15850 (Red 7), Ci 42090 (Blue 1 Lake)]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>What it is: </strong>The iconic Dior Addict Lip Maximizer plumping lip gloss gets a refresh with a new 90% natural-origin formula, a reimagined case and updated shades.</p>
<p><strong>Ingredient Callouts:</strong> Free of sulfates SLS and SLES, parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, triclosan, and triclocarban, and contains less than one percent of synthetic fragrances. This product is also vegan, cruelty-free, and gluten-free, and comes in recyclable packaging.</p>
<p><strong>What Else You Need to Know:</strong> Composed of 90% natural-origin ingredients and infused with cherry oil and hyaluronic acid, this Dior plumping lip gloss smooths and makes lips look bigger, leaving them hydrated for up to 24h. Now available in a new range of shiny shades with clear, intense, shimmering and holographic finishes.</p>
<p><strong>Clinical Results:</strong> In a clinical test on 28 subjects:</p>
<p>&#8211; 36%+ immediate volume effect &#8211; 48%+ smoother lips In an instrumental test on 30 subjects: &#8211; 24h hydration 90% natural-origin ingredients: Amount calculated based on the ISO 16128-1 and ISO 16128-2 standard. Water percentage included. The remaining ingredients contribute to the formula’s performance, sensory appeal and stability.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/dior-addict-lip-maximizer-plumping-gloss/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lip Glow Oil</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/lip-glow-oil/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/lip-glow-oil/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=507</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[#14375/A Hydrogenated Polyisobutene, Tridecyl Trimellitate, Polybutene, Pentaerythrityl Tetraisostearate, Phytosteryl/Octyldodecyl Lauroyl Glutamate, Ethylene/Propylene/Styrene Copolymer, Ethylhexyl Palmitate, Caprylic/Capric Triglyceride, Butylene/Ethylene/Styrene Copolymer, Parfum (Fragrance), Polyglyceryl-2 Triisostearate, Luffa Cylindrica Seed Oil, Prunus Avium (Sweet Cherry) Seed Oil, Trimethylolpropane Triisostearate, Diisostearyl Malate, Tocopherol, Pentaerythrityl Tetra-Di-T-Butyl Hydroxyhydrocinnamate, Undaria Pinnatifida Extract, Benzyl Alcohol, Propyl Gallate, [+/- :Ci 12085 (Red 36, Red 36 Lake), Ci 15850 (Red 6, Red 7, Red 7 Lake), Ci 15985 (Yellow 6, Yellow 6 Lake), Ci 17200 (Red 33), Ci 19140 (Yellow 5, Yellow 5 Lake), Ci 42090 (Blue 1, Blue 1 Lake), Ci 45380 (Red 21, Red 21 Lake, Red 22, Red 22 Lake), Ci 45410 (Red 27, Red 27 Lake, Red 28, Red 28 Lake), Ci 73360 (Red 30, Red 30 Lake), Ci 77163 (Bismuth Oxychloride), Ci 77491, Ci 77492, Ci 77499 (Iron Oxides), Ci 77742 (Manganese Violet), Ci 77891 (Titanium Dioxide), ].]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A nurturing, glossy lip oil that protects and enhances the lips, bringing out their natural color.</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:</b><br />
&#8211; Cherry Oil: Protects against stress factors and drying.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> Lip Glow Oil’s non-sticky, non-greasy, rich, and balmy texture combines the mirror shine of a lip gloss with the comfort of intense lip care. It’s enriched with cherry oil for a pampering formula. Featuring a minty-vanilla scent, it nurtures the lips with an immediate and lasting effect.</p>
<p>With its Color Reviver technology, Lip Glow Oil reacts directly to the moisture level in each woman&#8217;s lips for custom color while ensuring continual moisturization. The lips are more beautiful, even when bare, after five days of application.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/lip-glow-oil/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dior Addict Lip Glow</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/dior-addict-lip-glow/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/dior-addict-lip-glow/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=505</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<b>Suggested Usage:
</b>-Can be worn on its own as a lip balm for a subtle custom color-awakening effect and up to 24 hours of hydration.
-Can be worn under the corresponding shade of Dior Addict Lip Maximizer or Dior Addict Lip Glow Oil (both sold separately) to play with the color.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>An iconic Dior lip balm with 97 percent natural-origin ingredients that awakens the natural color of lips with a custom glow and up to 24 hours of hydration.<b></p>
<p>Formulation Type: </b>Lip Balm &amp; Treatment</p>
<p><b>Benefits: </b>Hydrating, Long-wearing, Plumping<br />
<b><br />
Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Cherry Oil: Protects against stress factors like drying.<br />
&#8211; Shea Butter: Provides comfort and nourishment.<br />
&#8211; Sunflower and Rice Waxes: Maintain shine.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, sulfates SLS &amp; SLES, triclocarban, triclosan, and contains less than one percent synthetic fragrance.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> The iconic Dior lip balm infused with color-reviver technology that adapts to the pH of lips to reveal a custom glow for up to six hours. Featuring cherry oil, shea butter, and sunflower waxes, Lip Glow offers both custom color and lip care. It’s available in a couture case and in shades to suit all skin tones.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/dior-addict-lip-glow/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gloss Bomb Universal Lip Luminizer</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/gloss-bomb-universal-lip-luminizer/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/gloss-bomb-universal-lip-luminizer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=503</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polybutene, Octyldodecanol, Bis-Diglyceryl Polyacyladipate-2, Tricaprylin, Microcrystalline Wax, Polyethylene, Silica Dimethyl Silylate, Vp/Eicosene Copolymer, Vp/Hexadecene Copolymer, Butyrospermum Parkii (Shea) Butter, Sorbitan Oleate, Silica, Octyldodecyl Neopentanoate, Ethylhexyl Palmitate, Calcium Sodium Borosilicate, Mica, Caprylyl Glycol, Butyrospermum Parkii (Shea) Butter Unsaponifiables, Aroma/Flavor, Benzyl Benzoate, Tribehenin, Pentaerythrityl Tetra-Di-T-Butyl Hydroxyhydrocinnamate, Fragrance, Tocopherol, Tocopheryl Acetate, Sorbitan Isostearate, Limonene, Synthetic Fluorphlogopite, Tetrahexyldecyl Ascorbate, Lactic Acid, Tin Oxide, Calcium Aluminum Borosilicate, Polyethylene Terephthalate, Palmitoyl Tripeptide-1, Acrylates Copolymer, Red 7 Lake (Ci 15850), Iron Oxides (Ci 77499, Ci 77491), Titanium Dioxide (Ci 77891).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>An ultimate, gotta-have-it lip gloss with explosive shine that feels as good as it looks.</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:</b><br />
&#8211; Shea Butter: Conditions skin.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens and phthalates. This product is also cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> This universal lip luminizer delivers explosive shine in six shades that flatter all skin tones. One swipe of Gloss Bomb’s XXL wand leaves lips looking instantly fuller and smoother. The non-sticky formula is super shiny, and has an addictive peach-vanilla scent you just can&#8217;t get enough of. Rihanna was obsessed with creating the perfect gloss that makes you want to put it on over and over again.<br />
“I made it because I wanted the girls to get kissed more.”—Rihanna, Brand Founder</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/gloss-bomb-universal-lip-luminizer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lip Soufflé Matte Cream Lipstick</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/lip-souffle-matte-cream-lipstick/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/lip-souffle-matte-cream-lipstick/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=501</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dimethicone, Methyl Trimethicone, Dimethicone Crosspolymer, Dimethicone/Vinyl Dimethicone Crosspolymer, Polyglyceryl-2 Triisostearate, Isododecane, 1,2-Hexanediol, Disteardimonium Hectorite, Phenoxyethanol, PEG-10 Dimethicone, Tocopheryl Acetate, Propylene Carbonate, Fragrance/Parfum, Linalool, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Oil, Gardenia Florida Fruit Extract, Nelumbo Nucifera (Sacred Lotus) Flower Extract, Nymphaea Odorata Root Extract, [+/- May Contain/Peut Contenir: Titanium Dioxide (CI 77891), Iron Oxides (CI 77491), Iron Oxides (CI 77499), Red 28 Lake (CI 45410), Red 27 (CI 45410), Red 7 Lake (CI 15850), Iron Oxides (CI 77492), Yellow 6 Lake (CI 15985), Yellow 5 Lake (CI 19140), Blue 1 Lake (CI 42090)].]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A weightless air-whipped lip cream that hugs lips with rich color and nourishing hydration that gives a soft velvety matte finish.</p>
<p><b>Formulation type:</b> Liquid lipstick</p>
<p><b>Benefits:</b> Hydrating</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of sulfates SLS and SLES, parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, triclosan, and triclocarban, and contains less than one percent of synthetic fragrances. This product is also vegan and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> This hydrating, whipped matte formula glides on for full-on color and a featherweight feel that stays comfortable all day with no drying or caking. Made with a botanical blend of lotus, gardenia, and white waterlily, plus Vitamin E, it nourishes while smoothing out lips with a soft blurring effect.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/lip-souffle-matte-cream-lipstick/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>With Gratitude Dewy Lip Balm</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/with-gratitude-dewy-lip-balm/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/with-gratitude-dewy-lip-balm/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:23:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=499</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[C12-15 Alkyl Ethylhexanoate, Diisostearyl Malate, Tridecyl Trimellitate, Ceresin, Bis-Diglyceryl Polyacyladipate-2, Butyrospermum Parkii (Shea) Butter, Vinyl Dimethicone/Methicone Silsesquioxane Crosspolymer, Hydrogenated Polyisobutene, Sorbitan Sesquioleate, 1,2-Hexanediol, Fragrance/Parfum, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Oil, Gardenia Florida Fruit Extract, Nelumbo Nucifera (Sacred Lotus) Flower Extract, Nymphaea Odorata Root Extract, Linalool. [+/- May Contain/Peut Contenir: Titanium Dioxide (CI 77891), Iron Oxides (CI 77491, CI 77492, CI 77499), Red 7 Lake (CI 15850), Blue 1 Lake (CI 42090)].]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A hydrating, nourishing balm with a buildable, light-to-medium dose of color and a natural dewy finish.</p>
<p><b>Formulation: </b>Lip Balm &amp; Treatment</p>
<p><b>Benefits:</b> Hydrating</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of sulfates SLS and SLES, parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, triclosan, and triclocarban, and contains less than one percent of synthetic fragrances. This product is also vegan and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> With a buildable dose of dewy color, this tinted lip balm wraps lips in weightless hydration that lasts all day, so they feel nourished and nurtured. With shea butter and a botanical blend of lotus, gardenia, and white waterlily, it cushions lips while building color so they look fuller and healthier.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/with-gratitude-dewy-lip-balm/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gloss Bomb Heat Universal Lip Luminizer + Plumper</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/gloss-bomb-heat-universal-lip-luminizer-plumper/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/gloss-bomb-heat-universal-lip-luminizer-plumper/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=497</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Shea Butter
-Vitamin E

Polybutene, Octyldodecanol, Bis-Diglyceryl Polyacyladipate-2, Tricaprylin, Cera Microcristallina/Microcrystalline Wax/Cire Microcristalline, Hydrogenated Polyisobutene, Polyethylene, Silica Dimethyl Silylate, Butyrospermum Parkii (Shea) Butter, Vp/Eicosene Copolymer, Sorbitan Oleate, Vp/Hexadecene Copolymer, Synthetic Fluorphlogopite, Silica, Ethylhexyl Palmitate, Caprylyl Glycol, Aroma/Flavor, Parfum/Fragrance, Octyldodecyl Neopentanoate, Mica, Butyrospermum Parkii (Shea) Butter Unsaponifiables, Tribehenin, Pentaerythrityl Tetra-Di-T-Butyl Hydroxyhydrocinnamate, Methyl Nicotinate, Sorbitan Isostearate, Tocopherol, Tocopheryl Acetate, Vanillyl Butyl Ether, Capsicum Frutescens Fruit Extract, Glycine Soja (Soybean) Oil, Zingiber Officinale (Ginger) Root Oil, Tetrahexyldecyl Ascorbate, Lactic Acid, Calcium Sodium Borosilicate, Calcium Aluminum Borosilicate, Palmitoyl Tripeptide-1, Tin Oxide, Benzyl Benzoate, Limonene, Iron Oxides (Ci 77491), Titanium Dioxide (Ci 77891).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A lip luminizer and plumper that delivers a hint of tint and fuller-looking lips.<br />
<b><br />
Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Shea Butter<br />
&#8211; Vitamin E</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens and phthalates. It is also gluten-free and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> Gloss Bomb Heat has an innovative Plump Job Complex that contains a blend of ingredients designed to gently plump lips for an undeniably fuller pout. The conditioning shea butter and vitamin E help lock in moisture for an intense wet-look shine finish.</p>
<p><b>Clinical Results:</b> In a consumer study of 30 volunteers:<br />
&#8211; 96% agreed it feels nourishing and provides a high-shine finish<br />
&#8211; 93% agreed it feels conditioning<br />
&#8211; 93% agreed it has a lush texture and makes lips look smoother</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/gloss-bomb-heat-universal-lip-luminizer-plumper/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stunna Lip Paint Longwear Fluid Lip Color</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/stunna-lip-paint-longwear-fluid-lip-color/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/stunna-lip-paint-longwear-fluid-lip-color/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=495</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Isododecane, Dimethicone, Trimethylsiloxysilicate, Hydrogenated Polycyclopentadiene, Disteardimonium Hectorite, Triethoxycaprylylsilane, Propylene Carbonate, Red 7 (Ci 15850), Yellow 5 Lake (Ci 19140), Yellow 6 Lake (Ci 15985).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A weightless, long-wearing, liquid lipstick with a soft-matte finish—born in a range of head-turning shades that look incredible on all skin tones.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens. This product is also cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> Stunna Lip Paint delivers high-impact color with low-maintenance, long wear in a range of universal shades handpicked by Rihanna. With one stroke of its lip-defining precision wand, Stunna’s weightless, comfortable, soft-matte formula stays kissably smooth all day.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/stunna-lip-paint-longwear-fluid-lip-color/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
