<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NARS &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<atom:link href="http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/danh-muc-san-pham/brands/nars/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:50:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>vi</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/favicon.png</url>
	<title>NARS &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Light Reflecting Advanced Skincare Foundation</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/light-reflecting-advanced-skincare-foundation/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/light-reflecting-advanced-skincare-foundation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=520</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Biomimetic Oat: Visibly improves clarity by reducing the appearance of redness.
-Japanese Lilyturf: Supports a strong skin barrier by helping maintain moisture.
-Cacao Peptides and Milk Thistle: Minimize the negative effect of blue light and environmental stressors.

Water/Aqua/Eau, C9-12 Alkane, Butylene Glycol, Undecane, Tridecane, Isodecyl Neopentanoate, Hydrogenated Polyisobutene, Polyglyceryl-6 Polyricinoleate, Polyglyceryl-2 Diisostearate, Disteardimonium Hectorite, Diisostearyl Malate, Glycerin, Synthetic Wax, Sodium Chloride, Ophiopogon Japonicus Root Extract, Ascophyllum Nodosum Extract, Theobroma Cacao (Cocoa) Seed Extract, Curcuma Longa (Turmeric) Root Extract, Silybum Marianum Fruit Extract, Aluminum Hydroxide, Magnesium Chloride, Sodium Dilauramidoglutamide Lysine, Tocopherol, Coco-Caprylate/Caprate, Ethylhexylglycerin, Pentylene Glycol, Hydroxyphenyl Propamidobenzoic Acid, Ascorbyl Palmitate, Citric Acid, Sea Water/Maris Aqua/Eau De Mer, Trisodium EDTA, Barium Sulfate, Alumina, Chlorphenesin, Phenoxyethanol, Potassium Sorbate, [+/-(May Contain/Peut Contenir): Iron Oxides (CI 77491, CI 77492, CI 77499), Mica, Titanium Dioxide (CI 77891)].]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>An advanced makeup-skincare-hybrid foundation with a natural finish that quickly blurs and smooths while visibly improving skin’s clarity over time.</p>
<p><b>Coverage: </b>Medium<br />
<b><br />
Finish: </b>Natural<br />
<b><br />
Formulation: </b>Liquid<br />
<b><br />
Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Biomimetic Oat: Visibly improves clarity by reducing the appearance of redness.<br />
&#8211; Japanese Lilyturf: Supports a strong skin barrier by helping maintain moisture.<br />
&#8211; Cacao Peptides and Milk Thistle: Minimize the negative effect of blue light and environmental stressors.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, sulfates SLS &amp; SLES, triclocarban, triclosan, and contains less than one percent synthetic fragrance. It is also vegan and comes in recyclable packaging.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> This breathable, medium-coverage, buildable foundation quickly conceals visible redness, blemishes, and dark spots while blurring the look of wrinkles, pores, and texture. Powered by 70 percent-skincare ingredients for visibly improved clarity plus Light Reflecting Complex for enhanced luminosity, the up to all-day-wear formula is suitable for most skin types, including sensitive.</p>
<p><b>Clinical Results:</b> In a clinical study of 31 women immediately after application:<br />
&#8211; It revealed a more even-looking skin tone by +93%</p>
<p>In a 6-week clinical study of 31 women:<br />
&#8211; It improved the appearance of skin clarity over time, even after makeup was removed</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/light-reflecting-advanced-skincare-foundation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Soft Matte Complete Concealer</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/soft-matte-complete-concealer/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/soft-matte-complete-concealer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:49:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=518</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dimethicone, Water, Glycerin, Butylene Glycol, Nylon-12, Paraffin, Dimethicone/Vinyl Dimethicone Crosspolymer, Dicaprylyl Carbonate, Zinc Oxide, Peg-10 Dimethicone, Peg-400, Sorbitan Sesquiisostearate, Microcrystalline Wax/Cera Microcristallina, Aluminum Hydroxide, Phenoxyethanol, Polysilicone-2, Silica, Barium Sulfate, Dextrin Palmitate, Distearyldimonium Chloride, Palmitic Acid, Hydrogen Dimethicone, Palmitoyl Tripeptide-5, Ascorbic Acid, Retinyl Palmitate, Tocopheryl Acetate, Alumina, Sodium Acetylated Hyaluronate, Tocopherol, [+/- (May Contain): Mica, Titanium Dioxide (Ci 77891), Iron Oxides (Ci 77491), Iron Oxides (Ci 77492), Iron Oxides (Ci 77499)].]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A full-coverage, oil-free concealer that conceals and blurs imperfections with a soft-matte, natural-looking finish.</p>
<p><b>Coverage:</b> Full</p>
<p><b>Finish:</b> Matte</p>
<p><b>Formulation:</b> Cream</p>
<p><b>Skin Type:</b> Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:</b><br />
&#8211; Peptides: Reduce appearance of wrinkles and pores over time.<br />
&#8211; Hyaluronic Acid: Reduce appearance of wrinkles and pores.<br />
&#8211; Antioxidants (Vitamins A, C, and E): Deliver Daily Defense.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of sulfates SLS and SLES, parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, oil, mineral oil, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, triclosan, and triclocarban, and contains less than one percent of synthetic fragrances. This product is also vegan and gluten-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> NARS’s Soft-Focus Smoothing Complex contains Optimal Diffusion Powder, which transforms the look of skin by blurring imperfections with light-diffusing spheres. The formula delivers all-day wear and high coverage that’s non-cakey, and won’t settle into fine lines and pores.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/soft-matte-complete-concealer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
