<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Makeup &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<atom:link href="http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/danh-muc-san-pham/makeup/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:54:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>vi</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/favicon.png</url>
	<title>Makeup &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Killawatt Freestyle Highlighter</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/killawatt-freestyle-highlighter/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/killawatt-freestyle-highlighter/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=525</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<b>Ginger Binge:</b>
Dimethicone, Talc, Isododecane, Synthetic Fluorphlogopite, Caprylic/Capric Triglyceride, Phenoxyethanol, Tin Oxide, Bismuth Oxychloride (CI 77163), Titanium Dioxide (CI 77891), Iron Oxides (CI 77491), Carmine (CI 75470), Yellow 5 Lake (CI 19140).

<b>Moscow Mule:</b>
Dimethicone, Synthetic Fluorphlogopite, Isododecane, Diisostearyl Malate, Polyethylene, Aluminum Calcium Sodium Silicate, Talc, Cetyl Dimethicone, Phenoxyethanol, Tin Oxide, Calcium Aluminum Borosilicate, Silica, Calcium Sodium Borosilicate, Titanium Dioxide (CI 77891), Bismuth Oxychloride (CI 77163), Manganese Violet (CI 77742), Iron Oxides (CI 77491, CI 77492), Carmine (CI 75470), Yellow 5 Lake (CI 19140).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A weightless, long-wear, cream-powder hybrid highlighter for the face and eyes in a range of shades, from subtle to supercharged, in solos and expertly-paired duos.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens and phthalates. This product is also cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> This long-wearing highlighter was born in a lineup of solos and duos for all skin tones. The cream-powder hybrid melts into skin and blends with almost zero effort. Loaded with superfine shimmer for an ultra-smooth, creamy texture, it’s your go-to for highlighting your face, eyes, and collarbone.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/killawatt-freestyle-highlighter/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eaze Drop Blurring Skin Tint</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/eaze-drop-blurring-skin-tint/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/eaze-drop-blurring-skin-tint/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:52:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=523</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Aqua/Water/Eau, Dimethicone, Dicaprylyl Carbonate, Talc, Isostearyl Neopentanoate, Peg-10 Dimethicone, Dimethicone/Vinyl Dimethicone Crosspolymer, Glycerin, Trimethylsiloxysilicate, Isododecane, Bis-Peg/Ppg-14/14 Dimethicone, Phenoxyethanol, Sodium Chloride, Dimethicone Crosspolymer, Magnesium Sulfate, Hydrogen Dimethicone, Sodium Dehydroacetate, Trehalose, Urea, Potassium Sorbate, Silica, Disteardimonium Hectorite, Aluminum Hydroxide, Benzoic Acid, Sodium Hyaluronate, C24-28 Alkyl Methicone, Pentylene Glycol, Serine, Dehydroacetic Acid, Propylene Carbonate, Ethylhexylglycerin, Algin, Caprylyl Glycol, Disodium Phosphate, Glyceryl Polyacrylate, Pullulan, Tocopherol, Potassium Phosphate, Iron Oxides (Ci 77491, Ci 77492, Ci 77499), Titanium Dioxide (Ci 77891).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>What it is: </strong>A lightweight, buildable light-to-medium coverage tinted moisturizer that leaves skin looking blurred and smoothed—In 25 flexible shades for all.</p>
<p><strong>Coverage: </strong>Light</p>
<p><strong>Finish: </strong>Natural</p>
<p><strong>Formulation: </strong>Liquid</p>
<p><strong>Ingredient Callouts:</strong> Free of parabens and phthalates. It is also vegan, gluten-free, and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><strong>What Else You Need to Know: </strong>This is an easy-to-apply, flexible skin tint Rihanna wanted to create. This tinted moisturizer quickly and visibly evens out complexion with a blurred effect. The HydraBlend complex and humidity-, sweat-, and transfer-resistant formula has a smooth texture that layers well with primer and skincare.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/eaze-drop-blurring-skin-tint/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Light Reflecting Advanced Skincare Foundation</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/light-reflecting-advanced-skincare-foundation/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/light-reflecting-advanced-skincare-foundation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=520</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Biomimetic Oat: Visibly improves clarity by reducing the appearance of redness.
-Japanese Lilyturf: Supports a strong skin barrier by helping maintain moisture.
-Cacao Peptides and Milk Thistle: Minimize the negative effect of blue light and environmental stressors.

Water/Aqua/Eau, C9-12 Alkane, Butylene Glycol, Undecane, Tridecane, Isodecyl Neopentanoate, Hydrogenated Polyisobutene, Polyglyceryl-6 Polyricinoleate, Polyglyceryl-2 Diisostearate, Disteardimonium Hectorite, Diisostearyl Malate, Glycerin, Synthetic Wax, Sodium Chloride, Ophiopogon Japonicus Root Extract, Ascophyllum Nodosum Extract, Theobroma Cacao (Cocoa) Seed Extract, Curcuma Longa (Turmeric) Root Extract, Silybum Marianum Fruit Extract, Aluminum Hydroxide, Magnesium Chloride, Sodium Dilauramidoglutamide Lysine, Tocopherol, Coco-Caprylate/Caprate, Ethylhexylglycerin, Pentylene Glycol, Hydroxyphenyl Propamidobenzoic Acid, Ascorbyl Palmitate, Citric Acid, Sea Water/Maris Aqua/Eau De Mer, Trisodium EDTA, Barium Sulfate, Alumina, Chlorphenesin, Phenoxyethanol, Potassium Sorbate, [+/-(May Contain/Peut Contenir): Iron Oxides (CI 77491, CI 77492, CI 77499), Mica, Titanium Dioxide (CI 77891)].]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>An advanced makeup-skincare-hybrid foundation with a natural finish that quickly blurs and smooths while visibly improving skin’s clarity over time.</p>
<p><b>Coverage: </b>Medium<br />
<b><br />
Finish: </b>Natural<br />
<b><br />
Formulation: </b>Liquid<br />
<b><br />
Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Biomimetic Oat: Visibly improves clarity by reducing the appearance of redness.<br />
&#8211; Japanese Lilyturf: Supports a strong skin barrier by helping maintain moisture.<br />
&#8211; Cacao Peptides and Milk Thistle: Minimize the negative effect of blue light and environmental stressors.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, sulfates SLS &amp; SLES, triclocarban, triclosan, and contains less than one percent synthetic fragrance. It is also vegan and comes in recyclable packaging.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> This breathable, medium-coverage, buildable foundation quickly conceals visible redness, blemishes, and dark spots while blurring the look of wrinkles, pores, and texture. Powered by 70 percent-skincare ingredients for visibly improved clarity plus Light Reflecting Complex for enhanced luminosity, the up to all-day-wear formula is suitable for most skin types, including sensitive.</p>
<p><b>Clinical Results:</b> In a clinical study of 31 women immediately after application:<br />
&#8211; It revealed a more even-looking skin tone by +93%</p>
<p>In a 6-week clinical study of 31 women:<br />
&#8211; It improved the appearance of skin clarity over time, even after makeup was removed</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/light-reflecting-advanced-skincare-foundation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Soft Matte Complete Concealer</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/soft-matte-complete-concealer/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/soft-matte-complete-concealer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:49:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=518</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dimethicone, Water, Glycerin, Butylene Glycol, Nylon-12, Paraffin, Dimethicone/Vinyl Dimethicone Crosspolymer, Dicaprylyl Carbonate, Zinc Oxide, Peg-10 Dimethicone, Peg-400, Sorbitan Sesquiisostearate, Microcrystalline Wax/Cera Microcristallina, Aluminum Hydroxide, Phenoxyethanol, Polysilicone-2, Silica, Barium Sulfate, Dextrin Palmitate, Distearyldimonium Chloride, Palmitic Acid, Hydrogen Dimethicone, Palmitoyl Tripeptide-5, Ascorbic Acid, Retinyl Palmitate, Tocopheryl Acetate, Alumina, Sodium Acetylated Hyaluronate, Tocopherol, [+/- (May Contain): Mica, Titanium Dioxide (Ci 77891), Iron Oxides (Ci 77491), Iron Oxides (Ci 77492), Iron Oxides (Ci 77499)].]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A full-coverage, oil-free concealer that conceals and blurs imperfections with a soft-matte, natural-looking finish.</p>
<p><b>Coverage:</b> Full</p>
<p><b>Finish:</b> Matte</p>
<p><b>Formulation:</b> Cream</p>
<p><b>Skin Type:</b> Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:</b><br />
&#8211; Peptides: Reduce appearance of wrinkles and pores over time.<br />
&#8211; Hyaluronic Acid: Reduce appearance of wrinkles and pores.<br />
&#8211; Antioxidants (Vitamins A, C, and E): Deliver Daily Defense.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of sulfates SLS and SLES, parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, oil, mineral oil, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, triclosan, and triclocarban, and contains less than one percent of synthetic fragrances. This product is also vegan and gluten-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> NARS’s Soft-Focus Smoothing Complex contains Optimal Diffusion Powder, which transforms the look of skin by blurring imperfections with light-diffusing spheres. The formula delivers all-day wear and high coverage that’s non-cakey, and won’t settle into fine lines and pores.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/soft-matte-complete-concealer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Diamond Bomb All-Over Diamond Veil</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/diamond-bomb-all-over-diamond-veil/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/diamond-bomb-all-over-diamond-veil/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:47:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=516</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polymethylsilsesquioxane, Phenyl Trimethicone, Calcium Sodium Borosilicate, Diisostearyl Malate, Dimethicone, Calcium Aluminum Borosilicate, Mica, Dimethicone/Vinyl Dimethicone Crosspolymer, Pentylene Glycol, Tin Oxide, Aqua/Water/Eau, Triethoxycaprylylsilane, Polyisobutene, Iron Oxides (Ci 77491), Titanium Dioxide (Ci 77891), Carmine (Ci 75470).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A diamond-dusted highlighter that delivers a 3D glittering veil of pure sparkle for face and body.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of sulfates SLS and SLES, parabens, and phthalates. This product is also gluten-free and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> Diamond Bomb has a 3D formula that’ll leave your face and body crystal-coated. It features a unique jelly-powder formula that’s cool to the touch, melts into skin, and creates an all-glitz-no-grit finish for all skin tones. Plus, it comes in a jewel-like compact you’ll never want to put down.</p>
<p>Diamond Bomb All-Over Diamond Veil was inspired by the crystal dress Rihanna wore at CFDA 2014.</p>
<p>&#8220;You can never have enough diamonds! This is the closest thing to bathing in it. The sparkle in this is just insane!&#8221;—Rihanna</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/diamond-bomb-all-over-diamond-veil/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Perfect Strokes Universal Volumizing Mascara</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/perfect-strokes-universal-volumizing-mascara/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/perfect-strokes-universal-volumizing-mascara/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=513</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Castor Oil: Conditions, softens, and nourishes lashes.

Water/Aqua/Eau, Copernicia Cerifera (Carnauba) Wax/Cera Carnauba/Cire de carnauba, Glyceryl Stearate, Hydrogenated Olive Oil Stearyl Esters, Synthetic Wax, Stearic Acid, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Wax, Palmitic Acid, Butylene Glycol, Polyacrylate-21, Olea Europaea (Olive) Oil Unsaponifiables, Aminomethyl Propanol, Ricinus Communis (Castor) Seed Oil, Synthetic Beeswax, Phenoxyethanol, Caprylyl Glycol, Galactoarabinan, Rhus Succedanea Fruit Wax, Shorea Robusta Resin, Hydroxyethylcellulose, Sodium Dehydroacetate, Xanthan Gum, Trideceth-6 Phosphate, Hydroxyacetophenone, Dipropylene Glycol, Glyceryl Caprylate, Tocopherol, Iron Oxides (CI 77499), Ultramarines (CI 77007).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A universal mascara with a unique eye-hugging brush to lift, lengthen, curl, and volumize every lash type for a lusher look.<br />
<b><br />
Formulation Type: </b>Volumizing, Curling, and Lengthening</p>
<p><b>Benefits: </b>Long-wearing<br />
<b><br />
Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Castor Oil: Conditions, softens, and nourishes lashes.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens. It is also vegan and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> Finding the perfect mascara comes down to your lash type, which differs from person to person. This weightless, easy-to-build formula and curvy, multi-length brush are made to give every lash type (fine/sparse, full/thick, straight, and curly) more lift, length, curl, and volume.</p>
<p><b>Clinical Results:</b> In an independent instrumental study of 120 subjects:<br />
&#8211; 100% of all lash types had more length and volume<br />
&#8211; 95% of all lash types had more lift<br />
&#8211; 92% of all lash types had more curl</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/perfect-strokes-universal-volumizing-mascara/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kind Words Lip Liner</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/kind-words-lip-liner/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/kind-words-lip-liner/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=511</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Trimethylsiloxysilicate, Isohexadecane, Synthetic Wax, Mica, Isododecane, Ethylhexyl Palmitate, Microcrystalline Wax/Cera Microcristallina/Cire microcristalline, Polybutene, Silica, C13-15 Alkane, VP/Hexadecene Copolymer, Copernicia Cerifera (Carnauba) Wax/Copernicia Cerifera Cera/Cire de carnauba, Paraffin, Ethylene/Propylene Copolymer, Fragrance/Parfum, Caprylyl Glycol, Diisostearyl Malate, Gardenia Florida Fruit Extract, Glyceryl Caprylate, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Oil, Nelumbo Nucifera Flower Extract, Nymphaea Odorata Root Extract, Polyglyceryl-2 Diisostearate, Linalool. +/- (May Contain/Peut Contenir) Titanium Dioxide (CI 77891), Iron Oxides (CI 77491, CI 77492, CI 77499), Red 7 Lake (CI 15850).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A super creamy, waterproof lip liner that glides on like a balm to define lips—in the same 10 rich, made-to-match shades as the Kind Words Matte Lipstick.<b></p>
<p>Formulation Type: </b>Lip Liner</p>
<p><b>Benefits: </b>Hydrating and Long-wearing</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, sulfates SLS &amp; SLES, triclocarban, and triclosan. It is also vegan, cruelty-free, and comes in recyclable packaging.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> Define and shape lips with one-swipe color and a soft matte finish. With an incredibly smooth, balm-like glide that won’t skip or tug, this waterproof liner not only stays put all day without smudging, but it keeps your lipstick in place, too. Keep the retractable tip sharp with the built-in sharpener.</p>
<p><b>Clinical Results:</b> In an independent consumer study of 51 people:<br />
&#8211; 100% said it draws smooth, even lines<br />
&#8211; 100% said lips don’t feel dry and that it’s comfortable to wear<br />
&#8211; 100% said it helps prevent lipstick from feathering or bleeding</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/kind-words-lip-liner/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dior Addict Lip Maximizer Plumping Gloss</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/dior-addict-lip-maximizer-plumping-gloss/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/dior-addict-lip-maximizer-plumping-gloss/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:36:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=509</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[001 Pink: #17318 Polyglyceryl-2 Triisostearate, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Oil, Hydrogenated Castor Oil Dimer Dilinoleate, Phytosteryl/Octyldodecyl Lauroyl Glutamate, Jojoba Esters, Polyglyceryl-2 Isostearate/Dimer Dilinoleate Copolymer, Candelilla Cera (Euphorbia Cerifera (Candelilla) Wax), Behenyl Behenate, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Wax, Butyrospermum Parkii (Shea) Butter, Oryza Sativa (Rice) Bran Wax, Caprylic/Capric Triglyceride, Parfum (Fragrance), Butyrospermum Parkii (Shea) Butter Unsaponifiables, Diisostearyl Malate, Prunus Avium (Sweet Cherry) Seed Oil, Trimethylolpropane Triisostearate, Tocopherol, Ethyl Vanillin, Ascorbyl Palmitate, Undaria Pinnatifida Extract, Propyl Gallate, [+/- Ci 77891 (Titanium Dioxide), Ci 77491, Ci 77499 (Iron Oxides), Ci 45380 (Red 21), Ci 15985 (Yellow 6 Lake), Ci 15850 (Red 7), Ci 42090 (Blue 1 Lake)]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>What it is: </strong>The iconic Dior Addict Lip Maximizer plumping lip gloss gets a refresh with a new 90% natural-origin formula, a reimagined case and updated shades.</p>
<p><strong>Ingredient Callouts:</strong> Free of sulfates SLS and SLES, parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, triclosan, and triclocarban, and contains less than one percent of synthetic fragrances. This product is also vegan, cruelty-free, and gluten-free, and comes in recyclable packaging.</p>
<p><strong>What Else You Need to Know:</strong> Composed of 90% natural-origin ingredients and infused with cherry oil and hyaluronic acid, this Dior plumping lip gloss smooths and makes lips look bigger, leaving them hydrated for up to 24h. Now available in a new range of shiny shades with clear, intense, shimmering and holographic finishes.</p>
<p><strong>Clinical Results:</strong> In a clinical test on 28 subjects:</p>
<p>&#8211; 36%+ immediate volume effect &#8211; 48%+ smoother lips In an instrumental test on 30 subjects: &#8211; 24h hydration 90% natural-origin ingredients: Amount calculated based on the ISO 16128-1 and ISO 16128-2 standard. Water percentage included. The remaining ingredients contribute to the formula’s performance, sensory appeal and stability.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/dior-addict-lip-maximizer-plumping-gloss/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lip Glow Oil</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/lip-glow-oil/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/lip-glow-oil/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=507</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[#14375/A Hydrogenated Polyisobutene, Tridecyl Trimellitate, Polybutene, Pentaerythrityl Tetraisostearate, Phytosteryl/Octyldodecyl Lauroyl Glutamate, Ethylene/Propylene/Styrene Copolymer, Ethylhexyl Palmitate, Caprylic/Capric Triglyceride, Butylene/Ethylene/Styrene Copolymer, Parfum (Fragrance), Polyglyceryl-2 Triisostearate, Luffa Cylindrica Seed Oil, Prunus Avium (Sweet Cherry) Seed Oil, Trimethylolpropane Triisostearate, Diisostearyl Malate, Tocopherol, Pentaerythrityl Tetra-Di-T-Butyl Hydroxyhydrocinnamate, Undaria Pinnatifida Extract, Benzyl Alcohol, Propyl Gallate, [+/- :Ci 12085 (Red 36, Red 36 Lake), Ci 15850 (Red 6, Red 7, Red 7 Lake), Ci 15985 (Yellow 6, Yellow 6 Lake), Ci 17200 (Red 33), Ci 19140 (Yellow 5, Yellow 5 Lake), Ci 42090 (Blue 1, Blue 1 Lake), Ci 45380 (Red 21, Red 21 Lake, Red 22, Red 22 Lake), Ci 45410 (Red 27, Red 27 Lake, Red 28, Red 28 Lake), Ci 73360 (Red 30, Red 30 Lake), Ci 77163 (Bismuth Oxychloride), Ci 77491, Ci 77492, Ci 77499 (Iron Oxides), Ci 77742 (Manganese Violet), Ci 77891 (Titanium Dioxide), ].]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A nurturing, glossy lip oil that protects and enhances the lips, bringing out their natural color.</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:</b><br />
&#8211; Cherry Oil: Protects against stress factors and drying.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> Lip Glow Oil’s non-sticky, non-greasy, rich, and balmy texture combines the mirror shine of a lip gloss with the comfort of intense lip care. It’s enriched with cherry oil for a pampering formula. Featuring a minty-vanilla scent, it nurtures the lips with an immediate and lasting effect.</p>
<p>With its Color Reviver technology, Lip Glow Oil reacts directly to the moisture level in each woman&#8217;s lips for custom color while ensuring continual moisturization. The lips are more beautiful, even when bare, after five days of application.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/lip-glow-oil/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dior Addict Lip Glow</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/dior-addict-lip-glow/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/dior-addict-lip-glow/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=505</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<b>Suggested Usage:
</b>-Can be worn on its own as a lip balm for a subtle custom color-awakening effect and up to 24 hours of hydration.
-Can be worn under the corresponding shade of Dior Addict Lip Maximizer or Dior Addict Lip Glow Oil (both sold separately) to play with the color.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>An iconic Dior lip balm with 97 percent natural-origin ingredients that awakens the natural color of lips with a custom glow and up to 24 hours of hydration.<b></p>
<p>Formulation Type: </b>Lip Balm &amp; Treatment</p>
<p><b>Benefits: </b>Hydrating, Long-wearing, Plumping<br />
<b><br />
Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Cherry Oil: Protects against stress factors like drying.<br />
&#8211; Shea Butter: Provides comfort and nourishment.<br />
&#8211; Sunflower and Rice Waxes: Maintain shine.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, sulfates SLS &amp; SLES, triclocarban, triclosan, and contains less than one percent synthetic fragrance.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> The iconic Dior lip balm infused with color-reviver technology that adapts to the pH of lips to reveal a custom glow for up to six hours. Featuring cherry oil, shea butter, and sunflower waxes, Lip Glow offers both custom color and lip care. It’s available in a couture case and in shades to suit all skin tones.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/dior-addict-lip-glow/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
