<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>innisfree &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<atom:link href="http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/tu-khoa-san-pham/innisfree/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 13:02:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>vi</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/favicon.png</url>
	<title>innisfree &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Green Tea Hyaluronic Acid Hydrating Toner</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/green-tea-hyaluronic-acid-hydrating-toner/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/green-tea-hyaluronic-acid-hydrating-toner/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 13:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=533</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-5 Types of Hyaluronic Acid: Provide more thorough, amplified hydration.
-Green Tea Tri-Biotics™: Hydrate and helps fortify skin’s moisture barrier.
-Panthenol: Helps nurture skin.
Water/Aqua/ Eau, Butylene Glycol, Propanediol, Glycerin, 1,2-Hexanediol, Trehalose, Panthenol, Polyglycerin-3, Ppg-13-Decyltetradeceth-24, Caprylic/Capric Triglyceride, Lactobacillus Ferment Lysate, Xanthan Gum, Ethylhexylglycerin, Fragrance/Parfum, Disodium Edta, Cellulose Gum, Camellia Sinensis Leaf Extract, Squalane, Camellia Sinensis Seed Oil, Lactic Acid, Linalool, Limonene, Sodium Hyaluronate, Hydrolyzed Hyaluronic Acid, Sodium Hyaluronate Crosspolymer, Hyaluronic Acid, Acrylates/Stearyl Methacrylate Copolymer, Tremella Fuciformis Sporocarp Extract, Sodium Acetylated Hyaluronate, Tocopherol, Ceramide Np.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A watery toner infused with green tea and hyaluronic acid to deliver thorough hydration and prep skin.<br />
<b>Skin Type:</b> Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><b>Skincare Concerns:</b> Dryness</p>
<p><b>Formulation:</b> Liquid</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; 5 Types of Hyaluronic Acid: Provide more thorough, amplified hydration.<br />
&#8211; Green Tea Tri-Biotics<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />: Hydrate and helps fortify skin’s moisture barrier.<br />
&#8211; Panthenol: Helps nurture skin.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, sulfates SLS &amp; SLES, triclocarban, triclosan, and contains less than one percent synthetic fragrance.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> This lightweight, moisturizing toner is packed with antioxidants and amino acids from a balanced blend of green tea extracts and skin-nourishing panthenol for a hydrated canvas, ready for the next steps in your skincare routine.</p>
<p><b>Clinical Results:</b> Based on a 2-week independent consumer study on 30 women ages 20 to 35:<br />
&#8211; 100% felt that the product applies smoothly<br />
&#8211; 96% felt skin was more hydrated<br />
&#8211; 93% felt that skin was soothed with hydration</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/green-tea-hyaluronic-acid-hydrating-toner/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Daily UV Defense Invisible Broad Spectrum SPF 36 Sunscreen</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/daily-uv-defense-invisible-broad-spectrum-spf-36-sunscreen/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/daily-uv-defense-invisible-broad-spectrum-spf-36-sunscreen/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=467</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Avobenzone 2.5%, Homosalate 7%, and Octisalate 4.3%

Water / Aqua / Eau, Butylene Glycol, Cyclopentasiloxane, Butyloctyl Salicylate, Ethylhexyl Methoxycrylene, Arachidyl Alcohol, Behenyl Alcohol, Glyceryl Stearate, Peg-100 Stearate, 1,2-Hexanediol, Polymethylsilsesquioxane, Cetyl Alcohol, Arachidyl Glucoside, Phenoxyethanol, Propanediol, Polyacrylate Crosspolymer-6, Octyldodecanol, Fragrance / Parfum, Xanthan Gum, Centella Asiatica Extract, Portulaca Oleracea Extract, Echium Plantagineum Seed Oil, T-Butyl Alcohol, Camellia Sinensis Leaf Extract, Ethylhexylglycerin, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Oil Unsaponifiables, Cardiospermum Halicacabum Flower/Leaf/Vine Extract, Tocopherol, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Oil, Glycerin, Hamamelis Virginiana (Witch Hazel) Leaf Extract, Citrus Unshiu Peel Extract, Opuntia Coccinellifera Fruit Extract, Orchid Extract, Camellia Japonica Leaf Extract, Citric Acid, Sodium Benzoate, Potassium Sorbate.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>What it is: </strong>A lightweight, daily Broad Spectrum SPF 36 sunscreen delivering invisible sun protection while hydrating and soothing skin &#8211; no white-cast, just glow!</p>
<p><strong>Skin Type: </strong>Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><strong>Skincare Concerns: </strong>Dryness</p>
<p><strong>Formulation: </strong>Lightweight Cream</p>
<p><strong>Highlighted Ingredients:</strong></p>
<p>&#8211; Green Tea: Nurtures skin with soothing hydration.</p>
<p>&#8211; Cica: Soothes skin and reduces visible signs of irritation.</p>
<p>&#8211; Sunflower Seed Oil: Delivers lightweight moisture to skin.</p>
<p><strong>Ingredient Callouts:</strong> Free of sulfates SLS and SLES, parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, triclosan, and triclocarban, and contains less than one percent of synthetic fragrances.</p>
<p><strong>What Else You Need to Know: </strong>This sunscreen is infused with a blend of green tea, cica, and sunflower seed oil for three-in-one benefits; it hydrates, soothes, and protects. The lightweight formula delivers undetectable sun protection with SPF 36 while giving skin giving a fresh-looking glow.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/daily-uv-defense-invisible-broad-spectrum-spf-36-sunscreen/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
