<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Masks &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<atom:link href="http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/danh-muc-san-pham/skincare/masks/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:24:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>vi</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/favicon.png</url>
	<title>Masks &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Party Recharge Hydrating Hyaluronic Under Eye Masks</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/party-recharge-hydrating-hyaluronic-under-eye-masks/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/party-recharge-hydrating-hyaluronic-under-eye-masks/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=464</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Hyaluronic Acid: Helps hydrates skin.
-Niacinamide: Balances skin.
-Real Crystal Extract: Cools the skin.

Aqua (Water), Glycerin, Methylpropanediol, Chondrus Crispus (Seaweed) Extract, Niacinamide, Sodium Hyaluronate, Diamond Powder, Nephrite Powder, Amethyst Powder, Tourmaline, Pearl Powder, Ruby Powder, Sapphire Powder, Silver, Potassium Chloride, Allantoin, Ceratonia Siliqua (Carob) Gum, Sucrose, Cellulose Gum, Xanthan Gum, Peg-60 Hydrogenated Castor Oil, Acrylates Copolymer, Ci 77000 (Aluminum), Polyethylene Terephthalate, Disodium Edta, Hydroxyacetophenone, 1,2-Hexanediol, Glyceryl Caprylate, Parfum (Fragrance).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A pair of sparkling, ultra-hydrating under-eye masks that recharges your eyes.</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Hyaluronic Acid: Helps hydrates skin.<br />
&#8211; Niacinamide: Balances skin.<br />
&#8211; Real Crystal Extract: Cools the skin.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens. It is also cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> These sparkling under-eye masks use a cooling hydrogel, with light-catching glitter, and hydrating and nourishing ingredients to visibly reduce puffiness and brighten dark circles. They are also made with hyaluronic acid to hydrate, while niacinamide balances and real crystal extract cools.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/party-recharge-hydrating-hyaluronic-under-eye-masks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hydrating Boob and Bum Sheet Mask Duo</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/hydrating-boob-and-bum-sheet-mask-duo/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/hydrating-boob-and-bum-sheet-mask-duo/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=462</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<b>Juicy Bits Boob Mask:</b>
Aqua (Water), Butylene Glycol, 1,2-Hexanediol, Glycerin, PEG-60 Hydrogenated Castor Oil, Bis-PEG-18 Methyl Ether Dimethyl Silane, Arginine, Carbomer, Ethylhexylglycerin, Erythritol, Caprylyl Glycol, Allantoin, Citrullus Lanatus (Watermelon) Fruit Extract, Disodium EDTA, Dipotassium Glycyrrhizate, Hydroxyethylcellulose, Adenosine, Rosa Canina (Rosehip) Seed Extract, Sodium Ascorbyl Phosphate, Sodium Hyaluronate, Polysorbate 60, Disodium Phosphate, Sodium Phosphate, Parfum (Fragrance).

<b>Feeling Cheeky Bum Mask:</b>
Aqua (Water), Butylene Glycol, 1,2-Hexanediol, Glycerin, PEG-60 Hydrogenated Castor Oil, Bis-PEG-18 Methyl Ether Dimethyl Silane, Arginine, Carbomer, Ethylhexylglycerin, Erythritol, Caprylyl Glycol, Allantoin, Disodium EDTA, Dipotassium Glycyrrhizate, Hydroxyethylcellulose, Salvia Hispanica (Chia) Seed Extract, Sodium Hyaluronate, Sodium Ascorbyl Phosphate, Prunus Persica (Peach) Fruit Extract, Polysorbate 60, Disodium Phosphate, Sodium Phosphate, Copper Tripeptide-1, Natto Gum, Acetyl Hexapeptide-8, Parfum (Fragrance).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A hydrating sheet mask duo for all skin types that’s designed to nourish and brighten the boobs and bum.</p>
<p><b>Skin Type: </b>Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><b>Skincare Concerns: </b>Dryness and Loss of Firmness and Elasticity</p>
<p><b>Formulation: </b>Mask</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> This product is vegan and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know: </b>This printed Boob and Bum Sheet Mask Duo moisturizes and firms the look of skin. Both are designed to keep your pair looking their perkiest and visibly uplifting your behind. These of-the-moment masks are enriched with vitamin C, hyaluronic acid, allantoin, rose extract, and watermelon extract to hydrate, visibly brighten, and nourish your assets. Enhanced with peptides, allantoin, and peach extract, these masks target dryness and fine lines—the perfect way to nourish your bum back to its bounciest-looking self.</p>
<p><b>This Set Contains:</b><br />
&#8211; 0.5 oz/ 15 mL Juicy Bits Boob Mask<br />
&#8211; 1.2 oz/ 35 mL Feeling Cheeky Bum Mask</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/hydrating-boob-and-bum-sheet-mask-duo/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryo Rubber™ Masks</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/cryo-rubber-masks/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/cryo-rubber-masks/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=460</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Hyaluronic Acid: Attracts moisture to skin.
-Kelp Extract: Supports moisture retention.
-Algae and Clay: Act as a cooling rubber mask.

<b>Step 1 Dr.Jart Hyaluronic Acid 1000 ppm Ampoule:</b>
Water/Eau, Dipropylene Glycol, Glycerin, Caprylic/Capric Triglyceride, Niacinamide, 1,2-Hexanediol, Butylene Glycol, PEG-240/HDI Copolymer Bis-Decyltetradeceth-20 Ether, Glyceryl Stearate, PEG-100 Stearate, Sorbitan Sesquioleate, Glycereth-26, Dimethicone, Cetearyl Alcohol, Trehalose, Mangifera Indica (Mango) Seed Butter, Macadamia Ternifolia Seed Oil, Sodium Hyaluronate, Glyceryl Acrylate/Acrylic Acid Copolymer, Ethylhexylglycerin, Disodium EDTA, Betaine, Allantoin, Melia Azadirachta Leaf Extract, Melia Azadirachta Flower Extract, Coccinia Indica Fruit Extract, Tocopherol, Potassium Laurate, Solanum Melongena (Eggplant) Fruit Extract, Aloe Barbadensis Flower Extract, Simmondsia Chinensis (Jojoba) Seed Oil, Ocimum Sanctum Leaf Extract, Curcuma Longa (Turmeric) Root Extract, Corallina Ofﬁcinalis Extract, Undaria Pinnatiﬁda Extract, Musa Sapientum (Banana) Fruit Extract, Cynara Scolymus (Artichoke) Leaf Extract, Brassica Oleracea Capitata (Cabbage) Leaf Extract, Asparagus Ofﬁcinalis Extract, Allium Cepa (Onion) Bulb Extract.

<b>Step 2 Dr.Jart Cryo Rubber Moisturizing Mask:</b>
Water/Eau, Methylpropanediol, Chondrus Crispus Extract, Glycerin, Xanthan Gum, Ceratonia Siliqua (Carob) Gum, Potassium Chloride, Dipropylene Glycol, Hydroxya- cetophenone, Sucrose, Panthenol, Polyglyceryl-10 Laurate, Algin, Titanium Dioxide/CI 77891, Caprylyl Glycol, Allantoin, Calcium Chloride, Melia Azadirachta Leaf Extract, Melia Azadirachta Flower Extract, Dipotassium Glycyrrhizate, Butylene Glycol, Ethylhexylglycerin, Coccinia Indica Fruit Extract, Disodium EDTA, Sodium Citrate, Citric Acid, Solanum Melongena (Eggplant) Fruit Extract, Aloe Barbadensis Flower Extract, Xylitylglucoside, Simmondsia Chinensis (Jojoba) Seed Oil, Anhydroxylitol, Ocimum Sanctum Leaf Extract, Curcuma Longa (Turmeric) Root Extract, Corallina Ofﬁcinalis Extract, Xylitol, Laminaria Japonica Extract*, Hydrogen Dimethicone, Glucose, Kaolin, Diatomaceous Earth.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A two-step, at-home kit designed to deliver active ingredients to ensure maximum skincare benefits.</p>
<p><b>Skin Type: </b>Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><b>Skincare Concerns: </b>Dryness, Redness, and Puffiness</p>
<p><b>Formulation: </b>Mask</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:</b><br />
&#8211; Prebiotic Complex (Ampoule): Helps treat specific skin concerns while working to balance the skin.<br />
&#8211; Algae and Clay (Rubber Mask)</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of sulfates SLS and SLES, parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, triclosan, and triclocarban, and contains less than one percent of synthetic fragrances.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know: </b>This innovative mask set packs the renewing effect of cryo-therapy in an at-home treatment. This collection includes the Cryo Rubber<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> with Soothing Allantoin to support skin&#8217;s natural healing process and protect from environmental irritants, while tiger grass addresses visible redness and irritation. The Cryo Rubber<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> with Moisturizing Hyaluronic Acid helps hydrate by attracting moisture from the atmosphere, while kelp extract boosts moisture retention to prevent water loss. The Cryo Rubber<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> with Brightening Vitamin C works together with niacinamide to lift away dead skin cells on the surface, while sea buckthorn fruit extract helps to visibly brighten the complexion. The Cryo Rubber<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> with Soothing Collagen helps smooth the look of fine lines and wrinkles and increase visible firmness, while carob fruit extract addresses skin&#8217;s natural collagen production.</p>
<p><b>This Set Contains:</b><br />
&#8211; Cryo Rubber<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> with Soothing Allantoin<br />
&#8211; Cryo Rubber<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> with Moisturizing Hyaluronic Acid<br />
&#8211; Cryo Rubber<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> with Brightening Vitamin C<br />
&#8211; Cryo Rubber<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> with Firming Collagen</p>
<p><b>Clinical Results: </b>In a clinical study of adult women aged 20 to 60, participants reported:<br />
Skin redness and red spots were reduced by:<br />
&#8211; 30.9% (Soothing Allantoin)<br />
&#8211; 29.0% (Brightening Vitamin C)<br />
&#8211; 28.1 % (Moisturizing Hyaluronic Acid)<br />
&#8211; 27.4% (Firming Collagen)</p>
<p>Skin temperature was temporarily reduced by:<br />
&#8211; 12.60°F (Firming Collagen)<br />
&#8211; 12.42°F (Moisturizing Hyaluronic Acid)<br />
&#8211; 12.06°F (Soothing Allantoin)<br />
&#8211; 11.34°F (Brightening Vitamin C)</p>
<p>Blood flow increased by:<br />
&#8211; 2.9% (Brightening Vitamin C)<br />
&#8211; 2.7% (Soothing Allantoin)<br />
&#8211; 2.6% (Moisturizing Hyaluronic Acid)<br />
&#8211; 2.6% (Firming Collagen)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/cryo-rubber-masks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
