<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Dr. Jart+ &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<atom:link href="http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/tu-khoa-san-pham/dr-jart/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:56:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>vi</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/favicon.png</url>
	<title>Dr. Jart+ &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ceramidin™ Skin Barrier Serum Toner</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/ceramidin-skin-barrier-serum-toner/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/ceramidin-skin-barrier-serum-toner/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=527</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Ceramide NP: Supports the skin barrier.
-Panthenol: Moisturizes and nourishes skin’s barrier to prevent water loss.

Water/Aqua/Eau, Dipropylene Glycol, Betaine, Propanediol, Alcohol Denat., Glycosyl Trehalose, Glycerin, 1,2-Hexanediol, Panthenol, Pentylene Glycol, Erythritol, Hydrogenated Starch Hydrolysate, Triethylhexanoin, Diphenyl Dimethicone, Polyglyceryl-10 Myristate, Ceramide Np, Sucrose Distearate, Ethylhexylglycerin, Sodium Hyaluronate, Theobroma Cacao (Cocoa) Seed Extract, Pelargonium Graveolens Flower Oil, Olea Europaea (Olive) Fruit Oil, Citrus Aurantium Bergamia (Bergamot) Fruit Oil, C12-14 Pareth-12, Hydrogenated Lecithin, Acrylates/C10-30 Alkyl Acrylate Crosspolymer, Tromethamine, Carbomer, Glyceryl Polymethacrylate, Glyceryl Stearate, Dextrin, Salvia Officinalis (Sage) Oil, Citronellol, Disodium Edta, Yellow 5 (Ci 19140).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A serum and toner that supports the skin barrier, moisturizes, softens, tones, and preps skin for the next step.</p>
<p><b>Skin Type:</b> Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><b>Skincare Concerns:</b> Dryness, Dullness, and Uneven Texture</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Ceramide NP: Supports the skin barrier.<br />
&#8211; Panthenol: Moisturizes and nourishes skin’s barrier to prevent water loss.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> This rich liquid combines your serum and toner step for one, potent skincare essential. As a serum, it glides on to form a moisturizing base layer that supports the skin barrier. As a toner, it removes residue and visibly refines skin’s texture. This serum toner is loaded with barrier-supporting ceramide NP and panthenol for moisture and barrier reinforcement.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/ceramidin-skin-barrier-serum-toner/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Premium BB Tinted Moisturizer with Niacinamide and SPF 40</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/premium-bb-tinted-moisturizer-with-niacinamide-and-spf-40/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/premium-bb-tinted-moisturizer-with-niacinamide-and-spf-40/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=473</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Glycerin: Rapidly moisturizes.

-Mineral and Chemical Sunscreens: Deliver UV protection.

-Niacinamide: Supports skin-barrier strength and protects against environmental stressors.

WATER/AQUA/EAU, CYCLOPENTASILOXANE, CYCLOHEXASILOXANE, GLYCERIN, PEG-10 DIMETHICONE, TALC, HEXYL LAURATE, DIPROPYLENE GLYCOL, C12-15 ALKYL BENZOATE, NIACINAMIDE, DIPHENYLSILOXY PHENYL TRIMETHICONE, DISTEARDIMONIUM HECTORITE, CITRUS AURANTIUM BERGAMIA (BERGAMOT) FRUIT OIL, CITRUS LIMON (LEMON) PEEL OIL, CITRUS AURANTIFOLIA (LIME) OIL, PINUS SYLVESTRIS (PINE) LEAF OIL, CITRUS AURANTIUM DULCIS (ORANGE) PEEL OIL, ADENOSINE, ALLANTOIN, ETHYLHEXYLGLYCERIN, TRIHYDROXYSTEARIN, POLYGLYCERYL-6 POLYRICINOLEATE, METHICONE, DIMETHICONE,DIMETHICONE/VINYL DIMETHICONE CROSSPOLYMER, 1,2-HEXANEDIOL, TRIETHOXYCAPRYLYLSILANE, MAGNESIUM SULFATE, EUCALYPTUS GLOBULUS LEAF OIL, LIMONENE, TOCOPHEROL, BHT, PHENOXYETHANOL, TITANIUM DIOXIDE (CI 77891), IRON OXIDES (CI 77492), IRON OXIDES (CI 77491), IRON OXIDES (CI 77499) &#60;ILN50730&#62;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>What it is: </strong>A multitasking, niacinamide-powered cream with a natural-looking finish that hydrates, conceals, and protects.</p>
<p><strong>Coverage: </strong>Light</p>
<p><strong>Finish: </strong>Natural</p>
<p><strong>Formulation: </strong>Cream</p>
<p><strong>SPF: </strong>Over 30</p>
<p><strong>Highlighted Ingredients:</strong></p>
<p>&#8211; Glycerin: Rapidly moisturizes.</p>
<p>&#8211; Mineral and Chemical Sunscreens: Deliver UV protection.</p>
<p>&#8211; Niacinamide: Helps improve skin&#8217;s barrier</p>
<p><strong>What Else You Need to Know:</strong> It’s your moisturizer, your makeup and your sunscreen in one. This BB Cream with SPF 40 seamlessly spreads over skin to deliver lightweight coverage with a natural finish that looks like you. This color corrector comes in 4 flexible, easy-to-navigate shades that adapt to a range of skin tones.</p>
<p><strong>Clinical Results:</strong> In a 3-day consumer study of 114 participants:</p>
<p>&#8211; 96% said skin tone looks even</p>
<p>&#8211; 97% said skin feels moisturized</p>
<p>&#8211; 96% said it feels weightless on skin</p>
<p>&#8211; 97% said it didn’t leave a white cast</p>
<p>&#8211; 96% said skin looks smoother</p>
<p>&#8211; 97% said skin looks brighter</p>
<p>&#8211; 96% said it leaves a natural looks-like-me finish</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/premium-bb-tinted-moisturizer-with-niacinamide-and-spf-40/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryo Rubber™ Masks</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/cryo-rubber-masks/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/cryo-rubber-masks/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=460</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Hyaluronic Acid: Attracts moisture to skin.
-Kelp Extract: Supports moisture retention.
-Algae and Clay: Act as a cooling rubber mask.

<b>Step 1 Dr.Jart Hyaluronic Acid 1000 ppm Ampoule:</b>
Water/Eau, Dipropylene Glycol, Glycerin, Caprylic/Capric Triglyceride, Niacinamide, 1,2-Hexanediol, Butylene Glycol, PEG-240/HDI Copolymer Bis-Decyltetradeceth-20 Ether, Glyceryl Stearate, PEG-100 Stearate, Sorbitan Sesquioleate, Glycereth-26, Dimethicone, Cetearyl Alcohol, Trehalose, Mangifera Indica (Mango) Seed Butter, Macadamia Ternifolia Seed Oil, Sodium Hyaluronate, Glyceryl Acrylate/Acrylic Acid Copolymer, Ethylhexylglycerin, Disodium EDTA, Betaine, Allantoin, Melia Azadirachta Leaf Extract, Melia Azadirachta Flower Extract, Coccinia Indica Fruit Extract, Tocopherol, Potassium Laurate, Solanum Melongena (Eggplant) Fruit Extract, Aloe Barbadensis Flower Extract, Simmondsia Chinensis (Jojoba) Seed Oil, Ocimum Sanctum Leaf Extract, Curcuma Longa (Turmeric) Root Extract, Corallina Ofﬁcinalis Extract, Undaria Pinnatiﬁda Extract, Musa Sapientum (Banana) Fruit Extract, Cynara Scolymus (Artichoke) Leaf Extract, Brassica Oleracea Capitata (Cabbage) Leaf Extract, Asparagus Ofﬁcinalis Extract, Allium Cepa (Onion) Bulb Extract.

<b>Step 2 Dr.Jart Cryo Rubber Moisturizing Mask:</b>
Water/Eau, Methylpropanediol, Chondrus Crispus Extract, Glycerin, Xanthan Gum, Ceratonia Siliqua (Carob) Gum, Potassium Chloride, Dipropylene Glycol, Hydroxya- cetophenone, Sucrose, Panthenol, Polyglyceryl-10 Laurate, Algin, Titanium Dioxide/CI 77891, Caprylyl Glycol, Allantoin, Calcium Chloride, Melia Azadirachta Leaf Extract, Melia Azadirachta Flower Extract, Dipotassium Glycyrrhizate, Butylene Glycol, Ethylhexylglycerin, Coccinia Indica Fruit Extract, Disodium EDTA, Sodium Citrate, Citric Acid, Solanum Melongena (Eggplant) Fruit Extract, Aloe Barbadensis Flower Extract, Xylitylglucoside, Simmondsia Chinensis (Jojoba) Seed Oil, Anhydroxylitol, Ocimum Sanctum Leaf Extract, Curcuma Longa (Turmeric) Root Extract, Corallina Ofﬁcinalis Extract, Xylitol, Laminaria Japonica Extract*, Hydrogen Dimethicone, Glucose, Kaolin, Diatomaceous Earth.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A two-step, at-home kit designed to deliver active ingredients to ensure maximum skincare benefits.</p>
<p><b>Skin Type: </b>Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><b>Skincare Concerns: </b>Dryness, Redness, and Puffiness</p>
<p><b>Formulation: </b>Mask</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:</b><br />
&#8211; Prebiotic Complex (Ampoule): Helps treat specific skin concerns while working to balance the skin.<br />
&#8211; Algae and Clay (Rubber Mask)</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of sulfates SLS and SLES, parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, triclosan, and triclocarban, and contains less than one percent of synthetic fragrances.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know: </b>This innovative mask set packs the renewing effect of cryo-therapy in an at-home treatment. This collection includes the Cryo Rubber<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> with Soothing Allantoin to support skin&#8217;s natural healing process and protect from environmental irritants, while tiger grass addresses visible redness and irritation. The Cryo Rubber<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> with Moisturizing Hyaluronic Acid helps hydrate by attracting moisture from the atmosphere, while kelp extract boosts moisture retention to prevent water loss. The Cryo Rubber<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> with Brightening Vitamin C works together with niacinamide to lift away dead skin cells on the surface, while sea buckthorn fruit extract helps to visibly brighten the complexion. The Cryo Rubber<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> with Soothing Collagen helps smooth the look of fine lines and wrinkles and increase visible firmness, while carob fruit extract addresses skin&#8217;s natural collagen production.</p>
<p><b>This Set Contains:</b><br />
&#8211; Cryo Rubber<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> with Soothing Allantoin<br />
&#8211; Cryo Rubber<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> with Moisturizing Hyaluronic Acid<br />
&#8211; Cryo Rubber<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> with Brightening Vitamin C<br />
&#8211; Cryo Rubber<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> with Firming Collagen</p>
<p><b>Clinical Results: </b>In a clinical study of adult women aged 20 to 60, participants reported:<br />
Skin redness and red spots were reduced by:<br />
&#8211; 30.9% (Soothing Allantoin)<br />
&#8211; 29.0% (Brightening Vitamin C)<br />
&#8211; 28.1 % (Moisturizing Hyaluronic Acid)<br />
&#8211; 27.4% (Firming Collagen)</p>
<p>Skin temperature was temporarily reduced by:<br />
&#8211; 12.60°F (Firming Collagen)<br />
&#8211; 12.42°F (Moisturizing Hyaluronic Acid)<br />
&#8211; 12.06°F (Soothing Allantoin)<br />
&#8211; 11.34°F (Brightening Vitamin C)</p>
<p>Blood flow increased by:<br />
&#8211; 2.9% (Brightening Vitamin C)<br />
&#8211; 2.7% (Soothing Allantoin)<br />
&#8211; 2.6% (Moisturizing Hyaluronic Acid)<br />
&#8211; 2.6% (Firming Collagen)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/cryo-rubber-masks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cicapair ™ Tiger Grass Camo Drops Color Corrector SPF 35</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/cicapair-tiger-grass-camo-drops-color-corrector-spf-35/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/cicapair-tiger-grass-camo-drops-color-corrector-spf-35/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=458</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Mineral Sunscreen (Zinc Oxide and Titanium Dioxide): Reflects UVA/UVB rays, protecting skin from sun damage.

Cyclopentasiloxane, <i>Centella asiatica</i> Extract, Isononyl Isononanoate, Butylene Glycol, Titanium Dioxide, Zinc Oxide, Glycerin, Niacinamide, Polymethylsilsesquioxane, Methyl Methacrylate Crosspolymer, Water, Sodium Chloride, Disteardimonium Hectorite, Iron Oxides (CI 77492), Aluminum Hydroxide, Triethoxycaprylylsilane, Acrylates/Dimethicone Copolymer, Chromium Oxide Greens, Beeswax, Disodium EDTA, Asiaticoside, Hydrogenated Lecithin, Lavandula Angustifolia (Lavender) Oil, Asiatic Acid, Rosmarinus Officinalis (Rosemary) Leaf Oil, <i>Centella asiatica</i> Leaf Water, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Oil, Houttuynia Cordata Extract, Alcohol, Caprylic/Capric Triglyceride, Phenoxyethanol, Anthemis Nobilis Flower Oil, Lecithin, Arnica Montana Flower Extract, Aniba Rosaeodora (Rosewood) Wood Oil, Ethylhexylglycerin, Madecassoside, Methyl Trimethicone, Butyloctyl Salicylate, Pentaerythrityl Tetraisostearate, Diphenysiloxy Phenyl Trimethicone, Dipropylene Glycol, Isododecane, Lauryl PEG-10 Tris (Trimethysiloxy) Silylethyl Dimethicone, Magnesium Sulfate, Polyglyceryl-4 Isostearate, Dipentaerythrityl Hexahydroxystearate / Hexastearate / Hexarosinate, 1,2-Hexanediol, Iron Oxides (CI 77491), Caprylyl Glycol, Synthetic Fluorphlogopite, Glyceryl Caprylate, Zein, Silica Dimethyl Silylate, Adenosine, Zea Mays (Corn) Starch, Citrus Paradisi (Grapefruit) Peel Oil, Dipotassium Phosphate, Calcium Stearate, Gossypium Herbaceum (Cotton) Seed Oil, Panthenol, Tocopherol, Anastatica Hierochuntica Extract, Pentylene Glycol, Magnesium Aspartate, Zinc Gluconate, Brassica Campestris (Rapeseed) Sterols, Leuconostoc / Radish Root Ferment Filtrate, Sucrose Laurate, Polyglyceryl-2 Caprate, Fragaria Vesca (Strawberry) Fruit Extract, Lysolecithin, Ceramide NP, Copper Gluconate, Sodium Ascorbyl Phosphate, Madecassic Acid.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A lightweight green-to-beige color corrector with a serum-like texture, dewy finish, and SPF to rapidly neutralize the look of redness and visibly ignite skin’s glow.</p>
<p><b>Skin Type:</b> Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><b>Skincare Concerns:</b> Redness and Dullness</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Mineral Sunscreen (Zinc Oxide and Titanium Dioxide): Reflects UVA/UVB rays, protecting skin from sun damage.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> For centuries, tigers in the Asian wetlands have rolled around in <i>Centella asiatica</i> (aka tiger grass or cica) to help heal their wounds. Taking inspiration from the tigers, this K-beauty favorite utilizes visibly reparative tiger grass to soothe, calm, and moisturize skin.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/cicapair-tiger-grass-camo-drops-color-corrector-spf-35/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cicapair™ Tiger Grass Sleepair Intensive Mask</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/cicapair-tiger-grass-sleepair-intensive-mask/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/cicapair-tiger-grass-sleepair-intensive-mask/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 10:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=440</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Dr.Jart+ Green Repair Solution: Containing <i>Centella asiatica</i> and a blend of herbs, minerals, a moisturizing humectant, and a probiotic ferment, this solution soothes skin with moisture.

Water/Eau, Dipropylene Glycol, Propanediol, Glycerin, Caprylyl Methicone, 1,2-Hexanedoil, Niacinamide, Trehalose, Vinyle Dimethicone, Butylene Glycol, Eryngium Maritimum Callus Culture Diltrate, Fusidium Coccineum Ferment Filtrate, Cetyl Dimethicone, Houttuynia Cordata Extract, Ilex Aquifolium (Holly) Leaf Extract, Diethiconol, Chondrus Crispus Extract, Achillea Millefolium Oil, Ammonium Acryloyldimethyltaurate/VP Copolymer, Acrylates/C10-30 Alkyl Acrylate Crosspolymer, Dehydroxanthan Gum, Polyvinyl Alcohol, Saccharum Officinarum (Sugarcane) Extract, Tromethamine, Caprylyl Glycol, Sodium Acrylate/Sodium Acryloyldimethyl Taurate Copolymer, Polyisobutene, Methylpropanedoil, Adenosine, Melisa Azadirachta Leaf Extract, Melia Azadirachta Flower Extract, Disodium EDTA, Caprylyl/Capryl Glucoside, Panthenol, Sorbitan Oleate, Bamboo Vinegar, Glycine Soja (Soybean) Peptide, Streptococcus Thermophilus Ferment, Madecassoside, Ethylhexlglycerin, Coccinia Indica Fruit Extract, Curcuma Longa (Tumeric) Root Extract, Ocimum Sanctum Leaf Extract, Amber Powder, Solanum Meaongena (Eggplant) Fruit Extract, Hedera Helix (Ivy) Extract, Dextrin, Theobroma Cacao (Cocoa) Seed Extract, Carallina Officinalis Extract, Moringa Olefiera Seed Oil, Asiaticoside, Centella Asiatica Leaf Extract, Asiatic Acid, Madecassic Acid, Calcium Chloride, Centella Asiatica Extract, Magnesium Sulfate.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A soothing, moisturizing mask that visibly improves skin texture and radiance while you sleep for soft, glowing skin.<br />
<b><br />
Skin Type:</b> Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><b>Skincare Concerns:</b> Dryness, Dullness, and Uneven Texture</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Dr.Jart+ Green Repair Solution: Containing <i>Centella asiatica</i> and a blend of herbs, minerals, a moisturizing humectant, and a probiotic ferment, this solution soothes skin with moisture.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, sulfates SLS &amp; SLES, triclocarban, triclosan, and contains less than one percent synthetic fragrance.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> This refreshing, intensive gel treatment moisturizes, boosts radiance, and visibly improves skin elasticity after a single use. Supporting the moisture barrier with intense hydration, it leaves tired, stressed skin looking healthy and revitalized. It’s also specially formulated for sensitive skin.</p>
<p>This product is an <i>Allure</i> Best of Beauty award winner.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/cicapair-tiger-grass-sleepair-intensive-mask/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
