<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Mascara &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<atom:link href="http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/danh-muc-san-pham/makeup/eyes/mascara/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:43:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>vi</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/favicon.png</url>
	<title>Mascara &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Perfect Strokes Universal Volumizing Mascara</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/perfect-strokes-universal-volumizing-mascara/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/perfect-strokes-universal-volumizing-mascara/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=513</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Castor Oil: Conditions, softens, and nourishes lashes.

Water/Aqua/Eau, Copernicia Cerifera (Carnauba) Wax/Cera Carnauba/Cire de carnauba, Glyceryl Stearate, Hydrogenated Olive Oil Stearyl Esters, Synthetic Wax, Stearic Acid, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Wax, Palmitic Acid, Butylene Glycol, Polyacrylate-21, Olea Europaea (Olive) Oil Unsaponifiables, Aminomethyl Propanol, Ricinus Communis (Castor) Seed Oil, Synthetic Beeswax, Phenoxyethanol, Caprylyl Glycol, Galactoarabinan, Rhus Succedanea Fruit Wax, Shorea Robusta Resin, Hydroxyethylcellulose, Sodium Dehydroacetate, Xanthan Gum, Trideceth-6 Phosphate, Hydroxyacetophenone, Dipropylene Glycol, Glyceryl Caprylate, Tocopherol, Iron Oxides (CI 77499), Ultramarines (CI 77007).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A universal mascara with a unique eye-hugging brush to lift, lengthen, curl, and volumize every lash type for a lusher look.<br />
<b><br />
Formulation Type: </b>Volumizing, Curling, and Lengthening</p>
<p><b>Benefits: </b>Long-wearing<br />
<b><br />
Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Castor Oil: Conditions, softens, and nourishes lashes.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens. It is also vegan and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> Finding the perfect mascara comes down to your lash type, which differs from person to person. This weightless, easy-to-build formula and curvy, multi-length brush are made to give every lash type (fine/sparse, full/thick, straight, and curly) more lift, length, curl, and volume.</p>
<p><b>Clinical Results:</b> In an independent instrumental study of 120 subjects:<br />
&#8211; 100% of all lash types had more length and volume<br />
&#8211; 95% of all lash types had more lift<br />
&#8211; 92% of all lash types had more curl</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/perfect-strokes-universal-volumizing-mascara/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Multi-Peptide Lash and Brow Serum</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/multi-peptide-lash-and-brow-serum/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/multi-peptide-lash-and-brow-serum/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=483</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Acetyl Tetrapeptide-3 in combination with Trifolium Pratense Flower Extract: Supports hair density and thickness.
-Biotinoyl Tripeptide-1 and Panthenol: Supports hair density and thickness.
-Combination of Camellia Sinensis Leaf Extract, Larix Europaea Wood Extract, and Zinc Chloride: Supports hair density and thickness.

Aqua, Glycerin, Butylene Glycol, Myristoyl Pentapeptide-17, Biotinoyl Tripeptide-1, Oligopeptide-2, Acetyl Tetrapeptide-3, Caffeine, Panthenol, Arginine, Glycine, Glycoproteins, Larix Europaea Wood Extract, Trifolium Pratense Flower Extract, Camellia Sinensis Leaf Extract, Dextran, Maltodextrin, Zinc Chloride, Hydroxyethylcellulose, Xanthan Gum, Trisodium Ethylenediamine Disuccinate, Polysorbate 20, Sodium Metabisulfite, Caprylyl Glycol, 1,2-Hexanediol, Sodium Benzoate, Benzoic Acid, Ethylhexylglycerin, Phenoxyethanol, Chlorphenesin.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>What it is: </strong>A concentrated, lightweight serum with four peptide technologies to promote the look of thicker, fuller, and healthier lashes and brows.</p>
<p><strong>Formulation:</strong> Lightweight Serum</p>
<p><strong>Highlighted Ingredients:</strong></p>
<p>&#8211; Acetyl Tetrapeptide-3 in combination with Trifolium Pratense Flower Extract: Supports hair density and thickness.</p>
<p>&#8211; Biotinoyl Tripeptide-1 and Panthenol: Supports hair density and thickness.</p>
<p>&#8211; Combination of Camellia Sinensis Leaf Extract, Larix Europaea Wood Extract, and Zinc Chloride: Supports hair density and thickness.</p>
<p><strong>Ingredient Callouts:</strong> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, sulfates SLS &amp; SLES, triclocarban, triclosan, and contains less than one percent synthetic fragrance. These products are also vegan, gluten-free, cruelty-free, and come in recyclable packaging.</p>
<p><strong>What Else You Need to Know:</strong> This twice daily treatment features 11 key active ingredients that work by targeting multiple pathways to support increased hair density and thickness while nourishing and protecting.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/multi-peptide-lash-and-brow-serum/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
