<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Dermalogica &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<atom:link href="http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/tu-khoa-san-pham/dermalogica/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:25:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>vi</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/favicon.png</url>
	<title>Dermalogica &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Precleanse Cleansing Oil</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/precleanse-cleansing-oil/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/precleanse-cleansing-oil/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=452</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Vitamin E: Nourishes and protects skin from damage.
-Rice Bran: Gently exfoliates.
-Rosemary: Protects skin from damage.

Caprylic/Capric Triglycerides, Prunus Armeniaca (Apricot) Kernel Oil, PEG-40 Sorbitan Peroleate, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Oil, Citrus Aurantium Dulcis (Orange) Oil, Citrus Grandis (Grapefruit) Peel Oil, Cymbopogon Schoenanthus Oil, Borago Officinalis Seed Oil, Lavandula Angustifolia (Lavender) Oil, Rosmarinus Officinalis (Rosemary) Leaf Extract, Solanum Lycopersicum (Tomato) Extract, Lavandula Hybrida Oil, Citrus Nobilis (Mandarin Orange) Peel Oil, Oryza Sativa (Rice) Bran Oil, Carthamus Tinctorius (Safflower) Seed Oil, Aleurites Moluccana Seed Oil, Cetyl Ethylhexanoate, Dicaprylyl Carbonate, Tocopheryl Acetate, Tocopherol, C12-15 Alkyl Benzoate, Citral, Limonene, Linalool.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A thoroughly cleansing oil that melts away waterproof makeup, SPF, debris, and oil without clogging pores or stripping your skin’s natural oils.</p>
<p><b>Skin Type:</b> Normal, Dry, Combination, and Oily</p>
<p><b>Skincare Concerns:</b> Pores, Redness, and Acne and Blemishes</p>
<p><b>Formulation:</b> Lightweight Oil</p>
<p><b>Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Vitamin E and Rice Bran Extract: Antioxidant-rich ingredients that moisturize, smooth, and soften skin.<br />
&#8211; Kukui Nut Oil and Borage Seed Oil: Supply vitamins A and C, as well as skin-barrier-supportive omega-3 fatty acids.<br />
&#8211; Apricot Kernel Oil: Soothes irritated skin, nourishes, and moisturizes.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, sulfates SLS &amp; SLES, triclocarban, triclosan, and contains less than one percent synthetic fragrance. It is also vegan, gluten-free, and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> An iconic formula from the brand known for the double cleanse, the Precleanse Cleansing Oil is a blend of lightweight plant-based oils that melt away layers of sebum (oil), SPF, waterproof makeup, and other impurities that build up on skin throughout the day. Gentle enough for the eyes, this formula will even remove eyelash glue.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/precleanse-cleansing-oil/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
