<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Fenty Beauty by Rihanna &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<atom:link href="http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/tu-khoa-san-pham/fenty-beauty-by-rihanna/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:54:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>vi</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/favicon.png</url>
	<title>Fenty Beauty by Rihanna &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Killawatt Freestyle Highlighter</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/killawatt-freestyle-highlighter/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/killawatt-freestyle-highlighter/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=525</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<b>Ginger Binge:</b>
Dimethicone, Talc, Isododecane, Synthetic Fluorphlogopite, Caprylic/Capric Triglyceride, Phenoxyethanol, Tin Oxide, Bismuth Oxychloride (CI 77163), Titanium Dioxide (CI 77891), Iron Oxides (CI 77491), Carmine (CI 75470), Yellow 5 Lake (CI 19140).

<b>Moscow Mule:</b>
Dimethicone, Synthetic Fluorphlogopite, Isododecane, Diisostearyl Malate, Polyethylene, Aluminum Calcium Sodium Silicate, Talc, Cetyl Dimethicone, Phenoxyethanol, Tin Oxide, Calcium Aluminum Borosilicate, Silica, Calcium Sodium Borosilicate, Titanium Dioxide (CI 77891), Bismuth Oxychloride (CI 77163), Manganese Violet (CI 77742), Iron Oxides (CI 77491, CI 77492), Carmine (CI 75470), Yellow 5 Lake (CI 19140).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A weightless, long-wear, cream-powder hybrid highlighter for the face and eyes in a range of shades, from subtle to supercharged, in solos and expertly-paired duos.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens and phthalates. This product is also cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> This long-wearing highlighter was born in a lineup of solos and duos for all skin tones. The cream-powder hybrid melts into skin and blends with almost zero effort. Loaded with superfine shimmer for an ultra-smooth, creamy texture, it’s your go-to for highlighting your face, eyes, and collarbone.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/killawatt-freestyle-highlighter/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eaze Drop Blurring Skin Tint</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/eaze-drop-blurring-skin-tint/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/eaze-drop-blurring-skin-tint/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:52:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=523</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Aqua/Water/Eau, Dimethicone, Dicaprylyl Carbonate, Talc, Isostearyl Neopentanoate, Peg-10 Dimethicone, Dimethicone/Vinyl Dimethicone Crosspolymer, Glycerin, Trimethylsiloxysilicate, Isododecane, Bis-Peg/Ppg-14/14 Dimethicone, Phenoxyethanol, Sodium Chloride, Dimethicone Crosspolymer, Magnesium Sulfate, Hydrogen Dimethicone, Sodium Dehydroacetate, Trehalose, Urea, Potassium Sorbate, Silica, Disteardimonium Hectorite, Aluminum Hydroxide, Benzoic Acid, Sodium Hyaluronate, C24-28 Alkyl Methicone, Pentylene Glycol, Serine, Dehydroacetic Acid, Propylene Carbonate, Ethylhexylglycerin, Algin, Caprylyl Glycol, Disodium Phosphate, Glyceryl Polyacrylate, Pullulan, Tocopherol, Potassium Phosphate, Iron Oxides (Ci 77491, Ci 77492, Ci 77499), Titanium Dioxide (Ci 77891).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>What it is: </strong>A lightweight, buildable light-to-medium coverage tinted moisturizer that leaves skin looking blurred and smoothed—In 25 flexible shades for all.</p>
<p><strong>Coverage: </strong>Light</p>
<p><strong>Finish: </strong>Natural</p>
<p><strong>Formulation: </strong>Liquid</p>
<p><strong>Ingredient Callouts:</strong> Free of parabens and phthalates. It is also vegan, gluten-free, and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><strong>What Else You Need to Know: </strong>This is an easy-to-apply, flexible skin tint Rihanna wanted to create. This tinted moisturizer quickly and visibly evens out complexion with a blurred effect. The HydraBlend complex and humidity-, sweat-, and transfer-resistant formula has a smooth texture that layers well with primer and skincare.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/eaze-drop-blurring-skin-tint/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Diamond Bomb All-Over Diamond Veil</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/diamond-bomb-all-over-diamond-veil/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/diamond-bomb-all-over-diamond-veil/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:47:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=516</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polymethylsilsesquioxane, Phenyl Trimethicone, Calcium Sodium Borosilicate, Diisostearyl Malate, Dimethicone, Calcium Aluminum Borosilicate, Mica, Dimethicone/Vinyl Dimethicone Crosspolymer, Pentylene Glycol, Tin Oxide, Aqua/Water/Eau, Triethoxycaprylylsilane, Polyisobutene, Iron Oxides (Ci 77491), Titanium Dioxide (Ci 77891), Carmine (Ci 75470).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A diamond-dusted highlighter that delivers a 3D glittering veil of pure sparkle for face and body.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of sulfates SLS and SLES, parabens, and phthalates. This product is also gluten-free and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> Diamond Bomb has a 3D formula that’ll leave your face and body crystal-coated. It features a unique jelly-powder formula that’s cool to the touch, melts into skin, and creates an all-glitz-no-grit finish for all skin tones. Plus, it comes in a jewel-like compact you’ll never want to put down.</p>
<p>Diamond Bomb All-Over Diamond Veil was inspired by the crystal dress Rihanna wore at CFDA 2014.</p>
<p>&#8220;You can never have enough diamonds! This is the closest thing to bathing in it. The sparkle in this is just insane!&#8221;—Rihanna</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/diamond-bomb-all-over-diamond-veil/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gloss Bomb Heat Universal Lip Luminizer + Plumper</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/gloss-bomb-heat-universal-lip-luminizer-plumper/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/gloss-bomb-heat-universal-lip-luminizer-plumper/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=497</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Shea Butter
-Vitamin E

Polybutene, Octyldodecanol, Bis-Diglyceryl Polyacyladipate-2, Tricaprylin, Cera Microcristallina/Microcrystalline Wax/Cire Microcristalline, Hydrogenated Polyisobutene, Polyethylene, Silica Dimethyl Silylate, Butyrospermum Parkii (Shea) Butter, Vp/Eicosene Copolymer, Sorbitan Oleate, Vp/Hexadecene Copolymer, Synthetic Fluorphlogopite, Silica, Ethylhexyl Palmitate, Caprylyl Glycol, Aroma/Flavor, Parfum/Fragrance, Octyldodecyl Neopentanoate, Mica, Butyrospermum Parkii (Shea) Butter Unsaponifiables, Tribehenin, Pentaerythrityl Tetra-Di-T-Butyl Hydroxyhydrocinnamate, Methyl Nicotinate, Sorbitan Isostearate, Tocopherol, Tocopheryl Acetate, Vanillyl Butyl Ether, Capsicum Frutescens Fruit Extract, Glycine Soja (Soybean) Oil, Zingiber Officinale (Ginger) Root Oil, Tetrahexyldecyl Ascorbate, Lactic Acid, Calcium Sodium Borosilicate, Calcium Aluminum Borosilicate, Palmitoyl Tripeptide-1, Tin Oxide, Benzyl Benzoate, Limonene, Iron Oxides (Ci 77491), Titanium Dioxide (Ci 77891).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A lip luminizer and plumper that delivers a hint of tint and fuller-looking lips.<br />
<b><br />
Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Shea Butter<br />
&#8211; Vitamin E</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens and phthalates. It is also gluten-free and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> Gloss Bomb Heat has an innovative Plump Job Complex that contains a blend of ingredients designed to gently plump lips for an undeniably fuller pout. The conditioning shea butter and vitamin E help lock in moisture for an intense wet-look shine finish.</p>
<p><b>Clinical Results:</b> In a consumer study of 30 volunteers:<br />
&#8211; 96% agreed it feels nourishing and provides a high-shine finish<br />
&#8211; 93% agreed it feels conditioning<br />
&#8211; 93% agreed it has a lush texture and makes lips look smoother</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/gloss-bomb-heat-universal-lip-luminizer-plumper/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fly Baby Mini Eye Primer and Liner Set</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/fly-baby-mini-eye-primer-and-liner-set/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/fly-baby-mini-eye-primer-and-liner-set/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=493</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<b>Pro Filt’r Amplifying Eye Primer:
</b>Isododecane, Trimethylsiloxysilicate, Cyclopentasiloxane, Mica, Talc, Polyethylene, Cyclohexasiloxane, Dextrin Palmitate/Ethylhexanoate, VP/Eicosene Copolymer, Triethylhexanoin, Disteardimonium Hectorite, Silica Silylate, Methicone, Propylene Carbonate, VP/Hexadecene Copolymer, Diisostearyl Malate, Tocopheryl Acetate, Polyglyceryl-2 Triisostearate, Dehydroacetic Acid, Titanium Dioxide (Ci 77891), Iron Oxides (Ci 77491, Ci 77492).

<b>Flyliner Longwear Liquid Eyeliner:
</b>Water, Butylene Glycol, Styrene/Acrylates Copolymer, Acrylates Copolymer, Styrene/Acrylates/Ammonium Methacrylate Copolymer, Beheneth-30, Pentylene Glycol, Alcohol, Caprylyl Glycol, 1,2-Hexanediol, Ethylhexylglycerin, Sodium Laureth-12 Sulfate, Disodium EDTA, C11-15 Pareth-7, Tetrasodium EDTA, Phenoxyethanol, Sodium Dehydroacetate, Potassium Sorbate, Black 2 (Ci 77266) (Nano).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A limited-edition set of Fenty Beauty eye essentials featuring a mini Pro Filt’r Amplifying Eye Primer and a mini Flyliner Longwear Liquid Eyeliner.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> Flyliner and Pro Filt’r Eye Primer go mini for this travel-friendly set. Pro Filt’r Eye Primer creates a smooth surface for effortless liner application. After priming lids, line eyes with Flyliner—a longwear, water-resistant liquid eyeliner with a flex tip and easy-grip triangle shape.</p>
<p><b>This Set Contains:</b><br />
&#8211; 0.006 oz/ 0.2 mL Flyliner Longwear Liquid Eyeliner in Cuz I’m Black<br />
&#8211; 0.11 oz/ 3.3 mL Pro Filt’r Amplifying Eye Primer in Invisipink</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/fly-baby-mini-eye-primer-and-liner-set/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pro Filt’r Soft Matte Longwear Liquid Foundation</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/pro-filtr-soft-matte-longwear-liquid-foundation/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/pro-filtr-soft-matte-longwear-liquid-foundation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=471</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Aqua/Water/Eau, Dimethicone, Talc, PEG-10 Dimethicone, Trimethylsiloxysilicate, Polypropylene, Isododecane, Cetyl PEG/PPG-10/1 Dimethicone, Nylon-12, HDI/Trimethylol Hexyllactone Crosspolymer, Phenoxyethanol, Sodium Chloride, Hydrogen Dimethicone, Glycerin, Magnesium Sulfate, Sodium Dehydroacetate, Disteardimonium Hectorite, Aluminum Hydroxide, Methicone, Benzoic Acid, Dehydroacetic Acid, Propylene Carbonate, Ethylhexylglycerin, Parfum/Fragrance, Silica, Biosaccharide Gum-4, Pentaerythrityl Tetra-Di-T-Butyl Hydroxyhydrocinnamate, Ananas Sativus (Pineapple) Fruit Extract, Carica Papaya (Papaya) Fruit Extract, Paullinia Cupana Seed Extract, Potassium Sorbate, Tocopherol, Sorbic Acid. May Contain/Peut Contenir (+/-): Titanium Dioxide (CI 77891), Iron Oxides (CI 77491, CI 77492, CI 77499).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A soft-matte, long-wearing foundation with climate-adaptive technology to fight heat, sweat, and shine—available in a wide range of shades.</p>
<p><b>Coverage: </b>Full<br />
<b><br />
Finish: </b>Matte<br />
<b><br />
Formulation: </b>Liquid<br />
<b><br />
Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens and phthalates. It is also vegan and cruelty-free.<b><br />
</b><br />
<b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> This buildable, medium-to-full-coverage foundation gives skin a visibly smooth, pore-diffused, shine-free finish. After doing extensive consumer testing and rigorous research, the brand refreshed its shade range to bring you the most inclusive formulation yet.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/pro-filtr-soft-matte-longwear-liquid-foundation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
