<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Eyes &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<atom:link href="http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/danh-muc-san-pham/makeup/eyes/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:43:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>vi</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/favicon.png</url>
	<title>Eyes &#8211; MY COSMETIC</title>
	<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Perfect Strokes Universal Volumizing Mascara</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/perfect-strokes-universal-volumizing-mascara/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/perfect-strokes-universal-volumizing-mascara/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=513</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Castor Oil: Conditions, softens, and nourishes lashes.

Water/Aqua/Eau, Copernicia Cerifera (Carnauba) Wax/Cera Carnauba/Cire de carnauba, Glyceryl Stearate, Hydrogenated Olive Oil Stearyl Esters, Synthetic Wax, Stearic Acid, Helianthus Annuus (Sunflower) Seed Wax, Palmitic Acid, Butylene Glycol, Polyacrylate-21, Olea Europaea (Olive) Oil Unsaponifiables, Aminomethyl Propanol, Ricinus Communis (Castor) Seed Oil, Synthetic Beeswax, Phenoxyethanol, Caprylyl Glycol, Galactoarabinan, Rhus Succedanea Fruit Wax, Shorea Robusta Resin, Hydroxyethylcellulose, Sodium Dehydroacetate, Xanthan Gum, Trideceth-6 Phosphate, Hydroxyacetophenone, Dipropylene Glycol, Glyceryl Caprylate, Tocopherol, Iron Oxides (CI 77499), Ultramarines (CI 77007).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A universal mascara with a unique eye-hugging brush to lift, lengthen, curl, and volumize every lash type for a lusher look.<br />
<b><br />
Formulation Type: </b>Volumizing, Curling, and Lengthening</p>
<p><b>Benefits: </b>Long-wearing<br />
<b><br />
Highlighted Ingredients:<br />
</b>&#8211; Castor Oil: Conditions, softens, and nourishes lashes.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens. It is also vegan and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> Finding the perfect mascara comes down to your lash type, which differs from person to person. This weightless, easy-to-build formula and curvy, multi-length brush are made to give every lash type (fine/sparse, full/thick, straight, and curly) more lift, length, curl, and volume.</p>
<p><b>Clinical Results:</b> In an independent instrumental study of 120 subjects:<br />
&#8211; 100% of all lash types had more length and volume<br />
&#8211; 95% of all lash types had more lift<br />
&#8211; 92% of all lash types had more curl</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/perfect-strokes-universal-volumizing-mascara/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fly Baby Mini Eye Primer and Liner Set</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/fly-baby-mini-eye-primer-and-liner-set/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/fly-baby-mini-eye-primer-and-liner-set/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=493</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<b>Pro Filt’r Amplifying Eye Primer:
</b>Isododecane, Trimethylsiloxysilicate, Cyclopentasiloxane, Mica, Talc, Polyethylene, Cyclohexasiloxane, Dextrin Palmitate/Ethylhexanoate, VP/Eicosene Copolymer, Triethylhexanoin, Disteardimonium Hectorite, Silica Silylate, Methicone, Propylene Carbonate, VP/Hexadecene Copolymer, Diisostearyl Malate, Tocopheryl Acetate, Polyglyceryl-2 Triisostearate, Dehydroacetic Acid, Titanium Dioxide (Ci 77891), Iron Oxides (Ci 77491, Ci 77492).

<b>Flyliner Longwear Liquid Eyeliner:
</b>Water, Butylene Glycol, Styrene/Acrylates Copolymer, Acrylates Copolymer, Styrene/Acrylates/Ammonium Methacrylate Copolymer, Beheneth-30, Pentylene Glycol, Alcohol, Caprylyl Glycol, 1,2-Hexanediol, Ethylhexylglycerin, Sodium Laureth-12 Sulfate, Disodium EDTA, C11-15 Pareth-7, Tetrasodium EDTA, Phenoxyethanol, Sodium Dehydroacetate, Potassium Sorbate, Black 2 (Ci 77266) (Nano).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A limited-edition set of Fenty Beauty eye essentials featuring a mini Pro Filt’r Amplifying Eye Primer and a mini Flyliner Longwear Liquid Eyeliner.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> Flyliner and Pro Filt’r Eye Primer go mini for this travel-friendly set. Pro Filt’r Eye Primer creates a smooth surface for effortless liner application. After priming lids, line eyes with Flyliner—a longwear, water-resistant liquid eyeliner with a flex tip and easy-grip triangle shape.</p>
<p><b>This Set Contains:</b><br />
&#8211; 0.006 oz/ 0.2 mL Flyliner Longwear Liquid Eyeliner in Cuz I’m Black<br />
&#8211; 0.11 oz/ 3.3 mL Pro Filt’r Amplifying Eye Primer in Invisipink</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/fly-baby-mini-eye-primer-and-liner-set/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stay Vulnerable Liquid Eyeshadow</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/stay-vulnerable-liquid-eyeshadow/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/stay-vulnerable-liquid-eyeshadow/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=491</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Isododecane, Synthetic Fluorphlogopite, Silica, Octyldodecanol, Hydrogenated Styrene/Isoprene Copolymer, Trimethylsiloxysilicate, Disteardimonium Hectorite, Mica, 1,2-Hexanediol, Caprylyl Glycol, Tocopheryl Acetate, Dicalcium Phosphate, Tin Oxide, Pentaerythrityl Tetra-di-t-butyl Hydroxyhydrocinnamate, Yellow 5 Lake (CI 19140), Blue 1 Lake (CI 42090), Iron Oxides (CI 77491), Iron Oxides (CI 77492), Manganese Violet (CI 77742), Titanium Dioxide (CI 77891).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A weightless, liquid-to-powder eyeshadow that blends seamlessly for a quick, buildable wash of long-lasting, waterproof, crease-resistant color.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, and sulfates SLS &amp; SLES. It is also cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> This quick and easy formula goes from liquid to powder in seconds. Velvety-smooth, creamy, and never sticky, it blends and builds easily before setting to a soft, satin finish that lasts all day—no creasing, smudging, fading, transferring, or drying out your skin.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/stay-vulnerable-liquid-eyeshadow/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>House of Lashes Iconic False Eyelashes</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/house-of-lashes-iconic-false-eyelashes/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/house-of-lashes-iconic-false-eyelashes/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=489</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Synthetic Fibers, Cotton Nylon Band.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>An eco-conscious and cruelty-free false lash collection that features House of Lashes&#8217; bestselling Iconic false lashes in Iconic, Iconic Lite, and Iconic Mini.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, sulfates SLS &amp; SLES, triclocarban, triclosan, and contains less than one percent synthetic fragrance. It is also vegan, gluten-free, cruelty-free, and comes in recyclable packaging.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> The lash with a name that says it all: Iconic lashes will transform any look from natural- or soft-glam to all-out glam. Whether you want the original and full style, Iconic, the more natural version, Iconic Lite, or the pair customized for smaller eyes, Iconic Mini, there’s an Iconic lash for all looks and eye shapes.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/house-of-lashes-iconic-false-eyelashes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brow Harmony Shape &#038; Fill Duo</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/brow-harmony-shape-fill-duo/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/brow-harmony-shape-fill-duo/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:09:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=487</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Isononyl Isononanoate, Mica, Nylon-12, Ethylhexyl Stearate, Dimethicone/Vinyl Dimethicone Crosspolymer, Boron Nitride, Lauroyl Lysine, Diisostearyl Malate, Ethylhexyl Palmitate, Calcium Silicate, Caprylyl Glycol, Dimethicone, Phenoxyethanol, Triethoxycaprylylsilane, Hexylene Glycol, Potassium Sorbate, [+/- May Contain/Peut Contenir: Iron Oxides (CI 77491, CI 77492, CI 77499), Titanium Dioxide (CI 77891)].]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is: </b>A waterproof brow putty that softly shapes and fills in brows for a natural, mistake-proof look that lasts.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of parabens. It is also cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b> This breakthrough putty glides on creamy and sets to a buildable powder finish, minus the powder fallout, for an instantly fuller, more defined look that won’t smudge. The complementary shades mimic brows’ gradient tones for the most natural-looking depth and dimension.</p>
<p><b>Clinical Results:</b> In an independent consumer study of 72 subjects:<br />
&#8211; 100% said it instantly fills in sparse brows for a natural look<br />
&#8211; 100% said it adheres to brows and doesn’t cake or flake<br />
&#8211; 98% said it’s smudgeproof and doesn’t transfer or rub off</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/brow-harmony-shape-fill-duo/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Perfect Strokes Matte Liquid Liner</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/perfect-strokes-matte-liquid-liner/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/perfect-strokes-matte-liquid-liner/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 12:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=485</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Water/Aqua/Eau, Styrene/Acrylates Copolymer, Propylene Glycol, Laureth-21, Pentylene Glycol, PEG-40 Hydrogenated Castor Oil, Phenoxyethanol, Ammonium Acrylates Copolymer, Caprylyl Glycol, PPG-2-Deceth-30, Sodium Dehydroacetate, Sodium Lauryl Sulfate, Disodium Laureth Sulfosuccinate, Black 2 (CI 77266)[NANO].]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>What it is: </strong>An easy-glide, waterproof liquid eyeliner with up to 800 vegan bristles to lay down long-lasting, ultra-black lines with perfect precision every time</p>
<p><strong>Ingredient Callouts:</strong> Free of sulfates SLS and SLES, parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, triclosan, and triclocarban, and contains less than one percent of synthetic fragrances. This product is also vegan and cruelty-free.</p>
<p><strong>What Else You Need to Know:</strong> The same rich, long-lasting formula—now with a new and improved brush! Revamped for smooth ink flow every time without leaking or drying out, the fine, flexible brush tip draws perfect strokes that won’t smudge, streak, or flake for a just-applied look all day. Shake well with cap on before use.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/perfect-strokes-matte-liquid-liner/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Multi-Peptide Lash and Brow Serum</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/multi-peptide-lash-and-brow-serum/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/multi-peptide-lash-and-brow-serum/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=483</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[-Acetyl Tetrapeptide-3 in combination with Trifolium Pratense Flower Extract: Supports hair density and thickness.
-Biotinoyl Tripeptide-1 and Panthenol: Supports hair density and thickness.
-Combination of Camellia Sinensis Leaf Extract, Larix Europaea Wood Extract, and Zinc Chloride: Supports hair density and thickness.

Aqua, Glycerin, Butylene Glycol, Myristoyl Pentapeptide-17, Biotinoyl Tripeptide-1, Oligopeptide-2, Acetyl Tetrapeptide-3, Caffeine, Panthenol, Arginine, Glycine, Glycoproteins, Larix Europaea Wood Extract, Trifolium Pratense Flower Extract, Camellia Sinensis Leaf Extract, Dextran, Maltodextrin, Zinc Chloride, Hydroxyethylcellulose, Xanthan Gum, Trisodium Ethylenediamine Disuccinate, Polysorbate 20, Sodium Metabisulfite, Caprylyl Glycol, 1,2-Hexanediol, Sodium Benzoate, Benzoic Acid, Ethylhexylglycerin, Phenoxyethanol, Chlorphenesin.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>What it is: </strong>A concentrated, lightweight serum with four peptide technologies to promote the look of thicker, fuller, and healthier lashes and brows.</p>
<p><strong>Formulation:</strong> Lightweight Serum</p>
<p><strong>Highlighted Ingredients:</strong></p>
<p>&#8211; Acetyl Tetrapeptide-3 in combination with Trifolium Pratense Flower Extract: Supports hair density and thickness.</p>
<p>&#8211; Biotinoyl Tripeptide-1 and Panthenol: Supports hair density and thickness.</p>
<p>&#8211; Combination of Camellia Sinensis Leaf Extract, Larix Europaea Wood Extract, and Zinc Chloride: Supports hair density and thickness.</p>
<p><strong>Ingredient Callouts:</strong> Free of parabens, formaldehydes, formaldehyde-releasing agents, phthalates, mineral oil, retinyl palmitate, oxybenzone, coal tar, hydroquinone, sulfates SLS &amp; SLES, triclocarban, triclosan, and contains less than one percent synthetic fragrance. These products are also vegan, gluten-free, cruelty-free, and come in recyclable packaging.</p>
<p><strong>What Else You Need to Know:</strong> This twice daily treatment features 11 key active ingredients that work by targeting multiple pathways to support increased hair density and thickness while nourishing and protecting.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/multi-peptide-lash-and-brow-serum/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eye Bento Bouncy Eyeshadow Trio</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/eye-bento-bouncy-eyeshadow-trio/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/eye-bento-bouncy-eyeshadow-trio/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinh Le]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:43:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/?post_type=product#038;p=481</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[01 Apricot Soda
CALCIUM TITANIUM BOROSILICATE, BIS-DIGLYCERYL POLYACYLADIPATE-2, TITANIUM DIOXIDE (CI 77891), CALCIUM SODIUM BOROSILICATE, POLYGLYCERYL-2 TRIISOSTEARATE, SYNTHETIC FLUORPHLOGOPITE, MICA (CI 77019), METHYLPROPANEDIOL, PROPANEDIOL, IRON OXIDES (CI 77491), TIN OXIDE, TRIETHOXYCAPRYLYLSILANE, IRON OXIDES (CI 77499), AQUA/WATER/EAU]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>What it is:</b> A stacked, creamy, powder eyeshadow in curated trios of shimmers or combinations of matte and shimmer shades.</p>
<p><b>Ingredient Callouts:</b> Free of sulfates SLS and SLES, parabens, and phthalates. Kaja is cruelty-free.</p>
<p><b>What Else You Need to Know:</b>These bouncy eyeshadows come packaged in bite-sized shimmer stacks or trios of matte and shimmer pigments that apply effortlessly with your fingertips. Kaja’s Glitter Arrangement Technology delivers uniform shimmer in every swipe—perfect for quick, easy eye looks on-the-go.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/Tinhle03/project1.github.io.git/san-pham/eye-bento-bouncy-eyeshadow-trio/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
